>> JEFF MAY HAVE -- THE RULES A
LITTLE BIT.
>> GUYS, IT WAS SO MUCH FUN
HAVING YOU HERE.
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR BEING
HERE.
WE'LL BE BACK TOMORROW.
SEE YOU THEN.
HAVE A GREAT NIGHT.
.
>>> CC SABATHIA PITCHING AN
EXTENDED REST TONIGHT MAKING HIS
FIRST START AGAINST THE REDS
SINCE 2012.
ACTUALLY HOMERED IN THIS
BALLPARK.
THAT WAS BACK IN 2005 WHEN HE
WAS WITH CLEVELAND.
GOING UP AGAINST JOEY VOTTO AND
THE REDS.
VOTTO IN THE LAST SEVEN GAMES,
FOUR HOMERS AND 14 RUNS BATTED
IN.
BASEBALL LIVE FROM CINCINNATI
WITH THE YANKEES AND REDS.
WE WELCOME YOU TO THE MLB.
NICE TO HAVE YOU JOINING US.
I'M CHRIS MYERS.
WHO WOULD HAVE THOUGHT, THE BEST
RECORD IN BASEBALL, THE REDS
HAVE IMPROVED OVER LAST YEAR
WHERE THEY WERE.
I'LL START WITH YOU AND THAT
YANKEE TEAM.
THE OFFENSE HAS BEEN EXPLOSIVE.
WE KNOW ABOUT AARON JUDGE AND
LEADING THE AMERICAN LEAGUE IN
HOME RUNS.
>> THE ROLE PLAYERS HAVE BEEN
PLAYING OUTSTANDING.
GUYS LIKE THAT HITTING AT THE
TOP OF THE LINEUP AS WELL.
NOW THAT GIVES THE HEART OF YOUR
LINEUP MORE CHANCE WITH RUNNERS
ON TO GET A CRACK AT IT.
YOU KNOW HOW IT IS GOING TO THE
BALLPARK.
WHEN EVERYBODY IS HITTING THE
BASEBALL IT'S FUN.
IT MAKES -- IF THEY CONTINUE TO
HIT THE BALL, THEY'LL BE AT THE
TOP OF THE DIVISION.
>> THE EXPERTS AND EVERYBODY HAS
THIS SENSE OF REBUILDING.
IN THE LOCKER ROOM THIS ISN'T
WHAT THEY WERE THINKING.
THE START THEY'VE GOTTEN OFF TO
IS NO SURPRISE AT ALL.
THIS IS THE FIRST TIME IN
DECADES THAT A YOUNG PROSPECT
HAS BEEN ABLE TO COME UP THAT
CRACK THAT LINEUP.
TO SEE THEM BUILD THE TEAM FROM
WITHIN IS AMAZING.
>> THERE IS A CONCERN.
WE KNOW THE YANKEE BULLPEN IS
TERRIFIC.
WHAT ABOUT THE STARTING
ROTATION?
>> HEALTH AS WELL.
THEY HAVE TO STAY HEALTHY.
THEY HAVE TO CONTINUE TO KEEP
GAMES CLOSE.
THEY WERE A LITTLE SHAKY THE
FIRST WEEK, BUT THEY SETTLED IN.
I THINK THEY FINALLY REALIZED WE
ARE THE KEY.
WE'RE ABLE TO KEEP GAMES CLOSE
AND KEEP UP STRIKING DISTANCE.
WE DON'T HAVE TO GO NINE.
WE CAN GO SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT.
>> LET'S ALSO TALK ABOUT THE
PERFECT BLEND OF VETERAN.
THEY HAVE SABATHIA, MATT
HOLLIDAY.
>> 21 WINS FOR THE YANKEES IN
CINCINNATI.
C.C. SABATHIA HAS BEEN GREAT.
HERE'S GARY SANCHEZ PLAYING HIS
TENTH GAME.
SEASON.
RUNNER UP ROOKIE OF THE YEAR
LAST YEAR.
t.
You may never even sit
in the back seat.
Yeah, but maybe you should.
♪  ♪
(Laughter)
♪♪
That's life.
You diet. You exercise.
And if you still need help
lowering your blood sugar...
...this is JARDIANCE.
Along with diet and exercise...
JARDIANCE lowers blood sugar
and A1C
in adults with type 2 diabetes.
JARDIANCE is also the only type
2 diabetes treatment with heart-
proven to reduce the risk
of cardiovascular death
in adults with type 2 diabetes
and cardiovascular disease.
JARDIANCE can cause serious side
effects, including dehydration.
This may cause you to feel
dizzy, faint, or lightheaded,
or weak upon standing.
Ketoacidosis is a serious side
effect that may be fatal.
Symptoms include nausea,
vomiting, stomach pain,
tiredness, and
trouble breathing.
Stop taking JARDIANCE and call
your doctor right away
if you have symptoms
of ketoacidosis
or an allergic reaction.
Symptoms of an allergic
reaction include rash,
swelling, and difficulty
breathing or swallowing.
Do not take JARDIANCE
if you are on dialysis
or have severe kidney problems.
Other side effects are sudden
kidney problems,
genital yeast infections,
increased bad cholesterol,
and urinary tract infections,
which may be serious.
Taking JARDIANCE with
a sulfonylurea or insulin
may cause low blood sugar.
Tell your doctor about all
the medicines you take
and if you have any
medical conditions.
So talk to your doctor
about JARDIANCE-
the one and only type 2 diabetes
treatment with heart.
Visit JARDIANCE.com for a free
consultation with
a Certified Diabetes Educator
if you qualify.
>>> COMING UP AFTER THE GAME,
"MLB WHIPAROUND."
TIM ADLEMAN, STATTON ISLAND
NATIVE PITCHING FOR THE REDS.
>> THANKS A LOT, CHRIS.
WE ARE ON THE BANKS OF THE OHIO
RIVER.
WHERE A GREAT AMERICAN BALLPARK
IN CINCINNATI WHERE TONIGHT IT'S
THE NEW YORK YANKEES AGAINST THE
CINCINNATI REDS.
>> BOOER WE'RE EXCITED ABOUT THE
MATCH-UP TONIGHT.
THE OTHER SURPRISE, THE
CINCINNATI REDS A HALF GAME OUT.
IT SHOULD BE A GOOD MATCH-UP.
NOT MANY PEOPLE EXPECTED THIS
MUCH FROM AT LEAST THIS EARLY.
WHO AM I DOING THE GAME WITH?
WE TRIED TO DECIDE WHO'S LOOKED
AT LIFE FROM BOTH SIDES NOW.
THIS IS THE GUY.
PAUL O'NEAL SPENT EIGHT SEASONS
WITH THE CINCINNATI REDS AND
NINE SEASONS WITH THE NEW YORK
YANKEES.
YOU SEE HIS NUMBERS.
ONE CHAMPIONSHIP WITH THE REDS
AND FOUR WITH THE NEW YORK
YANKEES.
SO HE'S SEEN IT AS WE SAID FROM
BOTH SIDES.
THIS IS EXCITING YANKEE TEAM
THAT WE'RE LOOKING AT RYE NOW.
I THINK THEY'VE SURPRISED
EVERYBODY.
THERE'S BEEN SOME INJURIES.
THEY'VE OVERCOME INJURIES.
ONE OF THE REASON THEY'VE BEEN
ABLE TO OVERCOME IT, AARON
JUDGE.
>> 6'7", 282 POUNDS.
I MEAN TO TELL YOU EVERY
HIGHLIGHT YOU'LL SEE THEY GO A
LONG WAY.
HE'S A HOME RUN HITTER.
460 FEET.
HE LEADS THE AMERICAN LEAGUE IN
HOME RUNS.
HE'S WAY AHEAD OF SCHEDULE.
HE'S DONE SOME THINGS ROOKIES
HAVE NEVER DONE IN THE GAME OF
BASEBALL.
>> HE'S SHOWN SOME PATIENCE AS
WELL AT THE PLATE.
PRETTY GOOD STUFF FOR HIM.
.317 AVERAGE.
FIRST IN SLUGGING PERCENTAGE IN
THE AMERICAN LEAGUE.
TIED FOR FIRST IN RBIs.
FIRST IN RUNS SCORED.
OUTSTANDING YEAR.
JOEY VOTTO IS NO ROOKIE, AND THE
BOTTOM LINE IS THIS TEAM CAN
HIT.
>> NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
JOEY VOTTO DOES HAVE SOME HELP.
THE REDS ARE SWINGING THE BATS.
JOEY VOTTO IS THE NEXT MVP.
HE IS THE REDS FACE.
HE KNOWS HOW TO HIT.
HE STAYS IN THE STRIKE ZONE.
ANOTHER HOME RUN LAST NIGHT.
HE'S HAD A PHENOMENAL HOME
STANCE.
JOEY VOTTO IN THE MIDDLE OF THIS
LINEUP IS AS GOOD AS IT GETS.
>> THEY'RE THE ONLY MAJOR LEAGUE
TEAM WITH THREE PLAYERS WITH
NINE OR MORE HOME RUNS.
VOTTO HAS TEN, SCHEBLER HAS
NINE, DUVALL HAS NINE.
AND THE REDS HAVE TAKEN THE
FIELD HERE AT GREAT AMERICAN
BALLPARK AND YOU SEE ADLEMAN
ABOUT TO START HIS WINE UP.
THEY'LL LEAD OFF THEIR LEFT
FIELDER BRETT GARDNER.
SANCHEZ WILL BAT SECOND.
THEN YOU'VE GOT CLEANUP, SAKOBY
ELLSBURY IN CENTER FIELD.
BATTING SIXTH IS SHORTSTOP
GREGORIUS.
BATTING EIGHTH AND PLAYING THIRD
IS RONALD TORREYES.
CC.C. SABATHIA WILL BAT NINTH.
ADLEMAN GETS THE START FOR THE
CINCINNATI REDS.
HE COMES IN WITH A 1-1 RECORD.
4.22 E.R.A.
FOUR WALKS.
20 STRIKEOUTS.
FIVE HOME RUNS.
OPPONENTS HITTING .244 AGAINST
HIM.
HE'S GOT THREE PITCHES,
FASTBALL, CURVEBALL, CHANGE.
MIXES THEM WELL.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT THE REDS
DEFENSIVELY.
DUVALL IN LAST.
HAMILTON IN CENTER.
SCHEBLER IS OVER IN RIGHT.
SUAREZ, COZART, PERAZA AND
VOTTO.
ADLEMAN ON THE MOUND.
TAKE A LOOK AT THE KEYS TO THE
GAME.
THEY ARE SPONSORED BY THE
LINCOLN MOTOR COMPANY.
PAUL, TELL ME HOW THIS GAME IS
GOING TO GO.
>> THE YANKEES OFFENSE IS
ROLLING.
JUST UNDER SIX RUNS PER GAME.
TEN RUNS LAST NIGHT.
THEY HAD NO SIGNS OF FATIGUE
FROM THE 18-INNING MARATHON THEY
PLAYED SUNDAY IN WRIGLEY.
REDS ARE SLUGGING TOO.
IF IT'S A BULLPEN BATTLE, IT
COULD BE A GOOD ONE.
YANKS FOURTH IN THE MLB AND THE
REDS ARE THIRD IN THE NATIONAL
LEAGUE.
UP TO THE STARTERS TO GET IN THE
BULLPEN.
>> THE YANKEES HAVE A SIX GAME
WINNING STREAK.
BOTH TEAMS ARE PLAYING WELL
COMING INTO THIS ONE.
BRETT GARDNER HAS BEEN ON FIRE
WITH AN 11-GAME HITTING STREAK.
HE'S READY.
ADLEMAN IS READY.
AND LET'S DO IT HERE IN
CINCINNATI.
THE FIRST PITCH IS A STRIKE AND
WE ARE UNDER WAY.
YANKEES SWEPT THREE FROM THE
CUBS AT WRIGLEY FIELD AND THE
FIRST ONE OF THIS SERIES AGAINST
THE REDS YESTERDAY.
>> YOU REMEMBER BRETT GARDNER IN
CHICAGO, BIG HOME RUN THAT
HOPING GAME.
THREE-RUN HOMER.
DOWN TO THEIR LAST STRIKE OF THE
LAST OUT.
THAT REALLY SET THE TONE FOR
THAT WHOLE SERIES.
>> HERE'S THE 1-1.
THERE'S A STRIKE.
SO THE COUNT 1-2.
THE YANKEES 21-9.
THE REDS ARE 17-15.
AP ABBREVIATED WIND-UP FOR
ADLEMAN.
A LOT OF PITCHERS ARE DOING
THAT.
THAT ONE'S POPPED UP.
SUAREZ WILL MAKE THE PLAY FOR
THE FIRST OUT.
SO ONE DOWN AND THAT WILL BRING
UP GARY SANCHEZ.
SANCHEZ ON THIS ROAD TRIP IS SIX
FOR 12.
ROAD TRIPS, FOUR GAMES AS WE
MENTIONED.
THE YANKEES HAVE WON ALL FOUR.
BOTH TEAMS HAVE AN OFF DAY
TOMORROW AND THEN THE REDS WILL
PLAY FOUR GAMES WITH SAN
FRANCISCO.
THE YANKEES GO BACK TO YANKEE
STADIUM AND THEY WILL PLAY FOUR
GAMES AGAINST THE HOUSTON
ASTROS.
FOUL BACK.
>> YOU SEE GARY SANCHEZ AND YOU
MENTIONED IT, MICHAEL.
HE'S JUST COMING BACK, SIX FOR
12.
HE'S BEEN BACK FROM A LITTLE
REHAB.
BUT HITTING CLOSER.
MUCH BETTER SLINGS LAST NIGHT AT
6-12.
WHAT A WAY TO GET BACK FROM WHAT
HE DID LAST YEAR.
>> THE 0-1.
HOW ABOUT THIS?
IN HIS LAST 13 PLATE
APPEARANCES, HE'S REACHED BASE
SAFELY 11 TIMES.
SIX HITS, FOUR WALKS AND HE WAS
HIT BY A PITCH ONCE.
1-1.
IT'S BLOWN.
2-1.
SANCHEZ BATTING SECOND IN THIS
LINEUP TODAY.
THEY MOVED HIM AROUND.
THEY LIKE HIM AT SECOND.
GETS MORE AT-BATS THAT WAY.
INSIDE.
3-1.
>> LAST NIGHT THE YANKEES HAD
THREE MEN HIT IN ONE INNING.
GARY SANCHEZ BEING ONE.
CHASE HEADLEY GOT HIT RIGHT ON
THE SIDE OF THE KNEE, PROBABLY A
BIG REASON WHY HE'S OUT OF THE
LINEUP TONIGHT.
>> 3-1.
FOULED BACK TO THE SCREEN.
3-2.
HEADLEY WENT TO BED LAST NIGHT
THINKING THAT HE WOULDN'T FIELD
VERY WELL TODAY.
HE SAID HE'S AVAILABLE IF THEY
NEED HIM LATE IN THE GAME BUT
THEY ARE GIVING HIM A REST JUST
TO CALM DOWN.
>> WHEN YOU COME FROM CHICAGO,
THE NIGHT BEFORE YOU GET IN AT
6:00, YOU'RE SO TIRED YOU DON'T
EVEN FEEL IT.
>> 3-2.
THAT ONE IS DRILLED DEEP TO LEFT
FEEL.
THERE IT GOES.
SEE YOU!
HOME RUN FOR GARY SANCHEZ, AND
THE YANKEES ARE ON THE BOARD.
>> NOT HIS FIRST HOME RUN, BUT
HIS SWINGS ARE GETTING BETTER
AND BETTER AND BETTER.
GARY SANCHEZ SO QUICK AND SO
POWERFUL.
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT, MOM MADE
THAT LITTLE GUY HAPPY EARLY IN
THE GAME.
THAT'S ALWAYS A BIG RELIEF TO
GET THAT FIRST ONE OUT OF THE
WAY.
GARY SANCHEZ UNBELIEVABLE
NUMBERS LAST YEAR.
>> THAT IS HIS FIRST SINCE
COMING OFF THE D.L.
HIS SECOND OVERALL.
HE'S BEEN LINING THE BALL.
THIS TIME HE LAUNCHED THIS.
>> FASTBALL KIND OF TAILS BACK
RIGHT TO THE BARREL.
NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
YOU SEE RIGHT OFF THE BAT.
YOU KNOW WHERE THAT'S HEADED.
>> PITCH OUTSIDE TO CASTRO.
>> HOW DOES THAT SOUND, MICHAEL?
>> LIKE A HOME RUN.
.448 FEET.
HIGH POP UP.
SHALLOW RIGHT CENTER.
SCHEBLER IS THERE.
HE'LL MAKE THE PLAY FOR THE
SECOND OUT.
>> WHEN YOU LOOK AT WHAT THE
YANKEES HAVE DONE, GETTING OFF
TO THIS START, THE BEST RECORD
IN BASEBALL, THEY'VE DONE IT
ESSENTIALLY WITHOUT SANCHEZ,
GREG BIRD WHO THEY PENCILED IN
TO DO BIG THINGS AT FIRST BASE.
HAD A ROUGH FIRST MONTH.
NOW ON THE DL WITH A BRUISED
BONE IN HIS RIGHT ANKLE.
THEY'VE BEEN ABLE TO FILL THE
SPOT.
THEY'VE BEEN ABLE TO GET THE JOB
GONE.
GREGORIUS STARTED THE SEASON ON
THE DL BUT PEOPLE HAVE PICKED IT
UP.
DIDI COMES BACK FROM THE DL AND
SWINGS THE BAT WELL.
SANCHEZ COMES BACK AND SWINGS
THE BAT WELL.
ALMOST LIKE WHEN YOU'RE PUT INTO
THE CONSIDERATION WHERE THE
--
INTO THE SITUATION.
THESE GUYS HAVE STEPPED RIGHT
BACK IN IT.
>> LOW, 2-0.
>> YOU SEE AARON JUDGE ON DECK.
IF YOU'RE A FAN, YOU'RE LOOKING
AT THAT.
IT'S MORE OF A BALANCE THING.
BALANCE OUT HIS RIGHTIES AND HIS
LEFTIES.
NO RHYME OR REASON REALLY IN THE
ORDER.
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
HE CAN PICK THEM OUT OF A HAT
NOW.
>> THE COUNT 3-0 ON ELLSBURY.
GOT OFF ON A NICE START.
HE BATTED CLEANUP A LOT.
.2904 HOMERS, 11 RBIs.
THERE'S A STRIKE.
IT WAS RAINING FOR MOST OF THE
DAY HERE IN CINCINNATI.
IT STOPPED EARLY AFTERNOON.
THEY'RE HOPING TO GET THIS GAME
IN.
RIGHT NOW NO RAIN WHATSOEVER.
3-1.
FLY BALL, LEFT FIELD.
DUVALL IS THERE.
HE'LL PUT IT AWAY WITH A FINAL
OUT OF THE INNING.
THE YANKEES GET A RUN AND GET IT
OFF THE BAT OF GARY SANCHEZ.
THE YANKEES CATCHER CRUSHES IT.
REDS COMING TO BAT.
Do not take VIAGRA if you
take nitrates for chest pain
or Adempas® for
pulmonary hypertension.
Your blood pressure could
drop to an unsafe level.
To avoid long-term injury,
seek immediate medical help
for an erection lasting
more than four hours.
Stop taking VIAGRA and
call your doctor right away
if you experience
a sudden decrease
or loss in vision or hearing.
Ask your doctor about
VIAGRA Single Packs.
If you have moderate to severe
rheumatoid arthritis like me,
and you're talking
to your rheumatologist
about a medication...
...this is HUMIRA.
This is HUMIRA helping
to relieve my pain...
...and protect my joints
from further damage.
HUMIRA has been clinically
studied for over 18 years.
HUMIRA works by targeting
and helping to...
...block a
specific source...
...of inflammation that
contributes to RA symptoms.
It's proven to help
relieve pain and...
...stop further joint
damage in many adults.
HUMIRA can lower your
ability to fight infections,
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections and cancers,
including lymphoma,
have happened,
as have blood, liver, and
nervous system problems,
serious allergic
reactions,
and new or worsening
heart failure.
Before treatment,
get tested for TB.
Tell your doctor
if you've been to areas...
...where certain fungal
infections are common
and if you've had TB,
hepatitis B,
are prone to infections,
or have flulike
symptoms or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA
if you have an infection.
Talk to your doctor
and visit HUMIRA.com
This is HUMIRA at work.
♪ ♪
Here comes the fun
with Sea-Doo.
♪ ♪
Sea-Doo has the most
affordable watercraft
on the market.
Starting at just $5,299
and get 0 percent financing.
Visit sea-doo.com today.
>> Michael:
>> Translator:
>> Michael: GARY SANCHEZ HAS
GIVEN THE YANKEES A 1-0 LEAD.
BILLY HAMILTON, OBVIOUSLY YOU
WANT TO KEEP HIM OFF THE BASE
PATH.
HE HAS 19 STOLEN BASES.
THAT PITCH IS HIGH AND OFF THE
GLOVE OF SANCHEZ.
YANKEES PLAYING FOR THE FRONT.
TORREYES IS IN AT THIRD.
NUMBERS ON SABATHIA, SIX STARTS,
33 INNINGS, 15 WALKS, 25
STRIKEOUTS.
HE'S ALLOWED SIX HOMERS.
TO SHORT, AND OVER TO FIRST.
ONE AWAY.
TAKE A LOOK AT THE REDS LINEUP.
WE JUST TOOK A LOOK AT BILLY
HAMILTON IN CENTER FIELD.
YOU'VE GOT JOE VOTTO.
CLEANUP HITTER IS ADAM DUVALL.
SUAREZ IS BATTING IN THE FIFTH
SPOT.
SCHEBLER IS IN RIGHT.
PERAZA AT SECOND.
HERE'S COZART.
NOW, THE REDS ARE ENDING A
NINE-GAME HOME STAND.
ON THE HOME STAND COZART HAS
HIT .346.
HE'S AT .351 OVERALL.
TAPPER TOWARDS SECOND.
CASTRO LETS IT PLAY HIM AND IT
GOES THROUGH HIS LEGS INTO
CENTER FIELD.
THAT WILL BE AN E-4.
>> Paul: YOU SAID IT.
HE KIND OF STOOD BACK.
DIDN'T KNOW WHETHER TO GO GET
THE HOP.
THE ALL OF A SUDDEN THE BALL
KIND OF PLAYED HIM.
NOT WHAT YOU'RE USED TO SEEING
COME UP.
THE BALL STAYED DOWN.
CASTRO HAS BEEN REALLY GOOD IN
THE FEEL.
ONCE IN A WHILE, THIS DOES
HAPPEN.
YOU SEE HE KIND OF HESITATES.
DOESN'T KNOW WHETHER TO COME IN
OR STAY BACK.
KIND OF CAUGHT RIGHT IN THE
MIDDLE.
>> Michael: THERE'S JOEY VOTTO.
HE'S BEEN ON FIRE OF LATE.
HITTING .358 OVER HIS LAST 67
AT-BAT.
SABATHIA COMES INSIDE.
1-0.
VOTTO CRUSHED A LONG HOME RUN
LAST NIGHT OFF TANAKA.
THAT MADE THE GAME 7-4 YANKEES,
BUT THE YANKS KEYS ADDED THREE
MORE AND RAN AWAY WITH IT.
VOTTO'S TENTH HOME RUN.
>> Paul: A GUY IN THE MAJOR
LEAGUES THAT REALLY HAS AN IDEA
OR A PLAN BUT HE WANTS TO DO
EVERY AT-BAT EVEN BROKEN DOWN TO
EVERY PITCH.
TALKING ABOUT JOEY VOTTO.
HE DOES NOT GET AWAY FROM WHAT
HE'S TRYING TO DO EVERY SINGLE
AT-BAT.
C.C.'S ALWAYS BEEN TOUGH ON
LEFTIES.
ZERO EXTRA BASE HITS.
ALL SIX HOME RUNS HAVE BEEN OFF
RIGHTY.
>> Michael: SEVEN STRIKEOUTS IN
14 AT-BATS.
2-0.
THERE'S A STRIKE.
>> Paul: THAT'S THE NEW C.C.
SABATHIA.
2-0 AND A LITTLE BREAKING BALL.
REMEMBER C.C. UP IN CLEVELAND
AND IN MILWAUKEE WHERE AT 2-0 HE
WAS GOING TO THROW IT BY YOU.
HE'S A DIFFERENT TYPE.
HE'S LEARNED TO ADJUST THE
VELOCITY THAT HE HAS NOW.
>> Michael: COUNT 3-1 ON VOTTO.
COZART IS AT FIRST.
HELD THERE BY CHRIS CARTER.
ON THE HOME STAND, 11 WALKS, ON
GREAT ON-BASE PERCENTAGE.
JUST A BIT HIGH, SO VOTTO WALKS.
C. DID
C.C. DID NOT LIKE THAT CALL.
THAT PUTS RUNNERS ON FIRST AND
SECOND FOR THE REDS.
ONE MAN OUT.
>> Paul: YOU TALKED ABOUT JOEY
VOTTO.
HIS WALKS OR -- THERE'S A REASON
FOR IT.
LITTLE CUT FASTBALL UP IN THE
STRIKE ZONE.
THIS HOLDS UP.
HE JUST DOES NOT GO OUT OF THE
STRIKE ZONE.
DRAMATIC TAKE THERE, WASN'T IT?
>> Michael: YEAH.
HERE'S DUVALL.
FIRST AND SECOND.
ONE MAN OUT.
IN THE BOTTOM OF THE FIRST
INNING.
YANKEES LEAD 1-0.
NOW, SABATHIA STRUGGLED HIS LAST
COUPLE STARTS.
HIS CUTTER HAS ABANDONED HIM
OVER THE LAST COUPLE GAMES.
JOE GIRARDI SAID HE HAS TO HAVE
THAT TONIGHT.
>> Paul: YOU'VE GOT TO REALLY
GET THAT BALL DOWN AND IN TO
RIGHTIES.
A LOT OF THESE CUTTERS HAVE BEEN
UP IN THE STRIKE ZONE.
NOT WHERE YOU WANT THEM.
BETTER ONE THERE.
THEY GET REAL FLAT UP IN THE
ZONE.
BUT KIND OF LIGHTS UP THE
HITTER'S EYES.
GOOD PITCH TO HIT.
GREAT SITUATION FOR A GOOD
CUTTER.
ANDY PETIT, YOU LOOK BACK AND
HE'S REALLY HELPED C.C. OVER THE
LAST YEAR.
IT'S A GREAT PITCH TO GET IN AND
GET A GROUND BALL, TURN A DOUBLE
PLAY.
>> Michael: 2-0.
FOULED AWAY.
2-1.
I WAS TALKING TO BRYAN PRICE
TODAY.
HE'S NOT SURPRISED AT HIS TEAM'S
GOOD START.
HE SAID WE'VE GOT A GOOD LINEUP.
WE CAN HIT WITH ANYBODY.
RIGHT NOW WE'RE 60% OF OUR
STARTING ROTATION OUT WITH
INJURY.
HE SAID WE'RE HOPING TO GET FIVE
INNINGS AND A LEAD OUT OF OUR
STARTERS BECAUSE OUR BULLPEN CAN
DO THE JOB.
THEY SEEM TO BE MISSING THAT ONE
PART OF THE TEAM AND THAT'S THE
STARTING ROTATION.
2-1.
HIGH FLY BALL.
CENTER FIELD IS DEEP.
GOING BACK ELLSBURY.
HE'S ON THE TRACK AND MAKES THE
PLAY.
FOR THE SECOND OUT.
BOTH RUNNERS TAG AND MOVE UP.
SO DUVALL DROVE ELLSBURY ALL THE
WAY BACK, BUT HE HAD JUST ENOUGH
REAL ESTATE TO HAUL IT IN.
>> Paul: KEPT HIM IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE FIELD IS WHAT KEPT HIM IN
THE BALLPARK.
JUST MISSED IT.
JUST COOL ENOUGH WHERE THE BALL
IS JUST NOT JUMPING LIKE IT
USUALLY DOES HERE.
SEE THAT JUST OFF THE END ENOUGH
TO KEEP IT IN THE BALLPARK.
LOOKS LIKE ELLSBURY DIDN'T
REALLY PICK IT UP OFF THE BAT.
GOOD BASE RUNNING BY VOTTO.
TAG UP FOR FIRST BASE.
>> Michael: HERE'S SUAREZ, ONE
OF THE BETTER PLAYERS YOU MIGHT
NOT KNOW THAT MUCH ABOUT.
OUTSTANDING THIRD BASEMAN
HITTING .327, SEVEN HOMERS, 22
RBIs.
>> Paul: SUAREZ, AGAIN, ANOTHER
GUY THAT'S HAD A GREAT HOME
STAND.
C.C. SABATHIA, YOU HAVE TO
REALIZE THE FIRST BASE IS OPEN.
I'M GOING TO MAKE MY BEST
PITCHES.
LEFTY ON DECK.
I'LL TAKE MY CHANCES THERE.
>> Michael: 0-1.
CHOPS SLOWLY TO THIRD.
TORREYES FIRES TO FIRST AND
SABATHIA GETS OUT OF TROUBLE.
NO RUNS.
NO HITS.
ONE ERROR AND TWO MEN LEFT.
AT THE END OF ONE IT'S 1-0 NEW
YORK.
everything in it.
Liberty did what?
Liberty Mutual paid to replace
all of our property
that was damaged.
And we didn't have to
touch our savings.
Yeah, our insurance
won't do that.
Well, there goes my boat.
You can leave worry behind
when Liberty stands with you™.
Liberty Stands With You™
Liberty Mutual Insurance
>> Michael: AARON JUDGE LEADS
OFF.
YANKEES LEAD 1-0.
JUDGE DID NOT PLAY LAST NIGHT.
KNEES HAVE BEEN SORE.
ICE PACKS AFTER HEAT GAME.
THEY GAVE HIM THE NIGHT OFF.
HE'S BACK IN THE LINEUP TONIGHT.
>> Paul: THOSE SHORT FENCES IN
THE RIGHT FIELD, YOU'RE GOING
OVER THERE, THEY LEAVE A MARK.
AND THOSE ARE THE THINGS
THROUGHOUT THE COURSE OF THE
SEASON THAT YOU FEEL.
AND IT STAYS AROUND FOR A FEW
DAYS.
YOU GET THE BUMPS AND THE
BRUISES AND YOU NEVER REALLY
HAVE ENOUGH TIME TO LET THINGS
REST.
>> Michael: LAST NINE GAMES H'S
BEEN ON FIRE.
13 RUNS BATTED IN.
>> Paul: KIND OF PITCHED AROUND
IN, OUT, UP, DOWN.
HOW HE'S GOING TO GO ABOUT IT,
OBVIOUSLY, HE'S GOT TO CHALLENGE
IT.
HE WENT WITH AN OFF-SPEED PITCH.
GOOD PITCH.
KIND OF TURNED OVER A CHANGE-UP.
GOOD MOVEMENT DOWN AND IN.
ALSO OUT IN FRONT.
>> Michael: HERE'S GREGORIUS.
THERE'S 1-0.
HIGH FLY BALL, DEEP RIGHT FIELD.
SCHEBLER BACK.
TURNING.
LOOKING SEE YOU!
HOME RUN FOR GREGORIUS.
AND THE YANKEES LEAD 2-0.
>> Paul: IT WAS KIND OF
TWILIGHT.
SCHEBLER GOING BACK ON THAT LIKE
HE HAD A CHANCE.
THIS BALL WAS CRUSHED.
AGAIN, ANOTHER GUY OFF THE
DISABLED LIST THAT JUST STEPPED
RIGHT BACK IN THE LINEUP.
DIDI IN THE WORLD BASEBALL
SERIES AND CAME BACK AND IT'S
LIKE HE NEVER MISSED A DAY.
YOU TALK ABOUT THE YANKEE
OFFENSE HOW EVERYTHING IS GOING.
YOU'VE GOT GUYS THAT ARE
TALKING, GUYS THAT ARE AVERAGE,
GUYS HITTING HOME RUNS.
YOU ADD IT ALL UP.
>> Michael: CARTER, A STRIKE.
>> Paul: DIDI KNOW ITS'S GONE.
>> Michael: 1-1.
THE OFFENSE HAS BEEN DOING IT.
HOME RUNS, RUNS PER GAME AND
WALKS.
THAT'S IN THE MAJOR LEAGUE.
DID HE GO?
NO, HE DID NOT.
THE COUNT 2-1.
>> Paul: CHRIS CARTER, .204.
HE HASN'T HAD A TON AT-BATS.
ONLY ONE HOME RUN.
HE WAS TIED FOR THE NATIONAL
LEAGUE LEAD LAST YEAR WITH 41
HOME RUNS.
HE ALSO DID STRIKEOUT 206 TIMES.
THEY BROUGHT HIM IN HERE AS KIND
OF AN INSURANCE POLICY.
SO FAR THEY'VE NEEDED HIM.
BIRD GOING DOWN, MATT HOLLIDAY
STILL OVER AT FIRST A LITTLE
BIT.
AWKWARD PLAYS LAST NIGHT.
CARTER IN THE LINEUP TODAY.
>> Michael: AND THE 3-2.
STRIKE THREE.
CARTER DOWN LOOKING.
>> Paul: LITTLE LOW.
>> Michael: TAKE A LOOK.
I'D SAY WAY LOW.
KIND OF HARD TO TAKE THAT WITH
TWO STRIKES.
>> Paul: I'D TAKE THAT WITH A
WALK TO FIRST.
>> Michael: HERE'S TORREYES.
UP AND AWAY.
1-0.
GROUND BALL, SHORT.
COZART.
GETS TORREYES.
THAT WILL DO IT HERE IN THE
SECOND.
BUT ANOTHER HOME RUN FOR THE
YANKEES.
THIS ONE OFF THE BAT OF
GREGORIUS.
2-0 NEW YORK.
During
ToyotaTime,
you can get
0% APR financing
on the 2017 RAV4
and over 10 other
select models.
Offer ends
May 31st.
For great deals
on other Toyotas,
visit Toyota.com.
Bom, bom de bom ba bom.
Toyota. Let's Go Places.
>> Michael: MLB ON FS1 SPONSORED
BY HARTFORD.
COUPLE OF SOLO HOME RUNS FOR THE
NEW YORK YANKEES AND THEY LEAD
THE REDS 2-0 AS WE GO TO THE
BOTTOM OF THE SECOND INNING.
HERE'S SCOTT SCHEBLER.
HE WILL LEAD OFF AGAINST
SABATHIA.
1-0.
>> Paul: NINE HOME RUNS.
LOOK UP AND DOWN THIS LINEUP.
NOT A LOT OF LEFTIES.
HE'S BEEN SO GOOD AGAINST
LEFTIES.
YOU KNOW, IF YOU'RE C.C. YOU
HAVE TO LOOK AT THOSE AS OUTS.
YOU'VE REALLY GOT TO MAKE YOUR
PITCHES SHUT DOWN THE LEFTIES
BECAUSE HE'S GOING TO FACE A
COUPLE RIGHTIES.
OR HE'S GOING TO HAVE SOME
ISSUES.
>> Michael: 2-0.
BASE HIT.
LEFT FIELD.
GARDNER COMES OVER.
GETS THE BALL IN.
LEADOFF SINGLE FOR SCHEBLER.
>> Paul: HITTING AGAINST A FULL
SHIP.
NOBODY HOME AT SHORTSTOP.
BALL GOT IN ON HIM A LITTLE BIT.
GOOD SWING.
ABSOLUTELY NOBODY HOME.
A LOT OF TIMES AS A HITTER YOU
HIT A BALL AND YOU KIND OF KNOW
THE VICINITY IT'S GOING.
YOU THINK IT'S RIGHT AT THE
SHORTSTOP AND YOU LOOK OUT THERE
AND THERE'S THAT SHIFT, THAT BIG
GAPING HOLE.
NICE.
>> Michael: HERE'S PERAZA, THE
SECOND BASEMAN.
AND A STRIKE FOR SABATHIA.
2-0 YANKEES.
BY SANCHEZ IN THE FIRST,
GREGORIUS IN THE SECOND.
YANKEES LOOKING TO SWEEP THIS
MINI TWO GAME SET.
REDS ACTUALLY VISIT NEW YORK
LATER ON THIS YEAR.
LINE DRIVE, BASE HIT.
STOPPING AT SECOND.
BASE HIT FOR PERAZA.
>> Paul: THIS GAME SO FAR
REMINDS ME A LOT OF LAST NIGHT
WHERE TANAKA GOT IN A LOT OF
JAMS AND PERAZA, A LOT OVER THE
PLATE AND JUST HAMMER ITS IN THE
HOLE.
TANAKA WAS ABLE TO MAKE THE
REALLY BIG PITCH.
HE'S GOT A COUPLE POP-UPS AND
DOUBLE PLAY WITH BASES LOADED.
C.C. GOES TO BAT WITH THEM IN
SCORING POSITION.
>> Michael: HERE'S MESORACO.
MESORACO.
HE STARTED THE SEASON REHABBING.
THAT'S WHY HIS NUMBER IS
JUST .250, ONE HOME RUN, ONE
BATTED IN.
>> Paul: HERE'S A GUY THAT'S IN
CONTACT.
HE WAS THE GUY.
SHOWING ALL KIND OF PROMISE
OFFENSIVELY.
YOU TALKED ABOUT T A COUPLE
SURGERIES.
>> Michael: 2015, A FOUR YEAR
$28 MILLION DEAL THEY COMMITTED.
AND THE PITCH.
3-0, SABATHIA.
PROBABLY WOULD HAVE GOTTEN A
STRIKE ON THAT ONE.
NOW 3-0 AS.
NOW BARKSDALE IS BARKING AT THE
YANKEE DUGOUT.
YOU CAN HEAR HIM SAY THE BALL
WAS OUTSIDE.
AND THE 3-0.
AND THAT'S UPSTAIRS AND THE
BASES ARE LOADED WITH REDS.
COUPLE OF SINGLES AND A WALK.
NOW A MEETING AT THE MOUND.
YOU SEE THE STRIKE BALL RATIO,
NOT GOOD.
AND THE REDS HAVE THE BASES
LOADED WITH NOBODY OUT.
HERE'S TIM ADLEMAN.
1 FOR 6 THIS YEAR WITH ONE
STACKED BUNT.
HE HAS DRIVEN IN TWO.
AND THE PITCH.
THERE'S A STRIKE.
STRIKE TWO.
THERE'S THE CUTTER HE NEEDS.
0-2.
>> Paul: A LOT OF TIME.
YOU HAVE TO REMIND YOURSELF IF
YOU'RE C.C. SABATHIA, THOUGH,
YOU PITCH IN THE AMERICAN LEAGUE
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN YOU'VE GOT A
PITCHER UP THERE.
YOU'RE ALMOST LOOKING FOR THAT
GROUND BALL.
I DON'T KNOW IF HE WANTS THE
STRIKEOUT AT THIS POINT.
TRY TO GET A DOUBLE PLAY.
>> Michael: SWING AND A MISS.
SO ADLEMAN GOES DOWN ON STRIKES
FOR THE FIRST OUT.
THAT WILL BRING UP BILLY
HAMILTON.
>> Paul: THAT BREAKING BALL C.C.
HAS THROWN ALL NIGHT.
THREW A CURVEBALL HERE.
LOOK HOW MUCH BIGGER THE BREAK
IS.
>> Michael: HAMILTON HAD NOT HIT
INTO A DOUBLE PLAY ALL YEAR
BEFORE LAST NIGHT.
HE HIT INTO TWO LAST NIGHT.
THAT'S THE FIRST TIME IN HIS
CAREER HE HAS EVER HIT INTO TWO
DOUBLE PLAYS.
ONE OF THE FASTEST MEN ON THE
PLANET, SO VERY TOUGH TO DOUBLE
HIM UP.
>> Paul: EVEN WITH A HEAD START?
>> Michael: COUNT 1-0.
>> Paul: THE OHIO RIVER.
WE'RE ON THIS SIDE.
KENTUCKY OVER THERE.
>> Michael: 2-0.
OBVIOUSLY NO PLACE TO PUT
HAMILTON.
BASES LOADED.
ONE OUT.
YANKEES UP 2-0.
WAY INSIDE.
HAMILTON, 3-0.
>> Paul:
>> Paul: C.C. RIGHT HERE, YOU'VE
GOT TO MAKE A COUPLE GOOD
PITCHES.
HOPE YOU CAN KEEP THE GRAND JURY
-- DAMAGE UNDER CONTROL.
IT AN OFFENSIVE FIELD.
NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
YOU SEE THE OFFENSIVE NUMBERS
THE REDS PUT UP EVERY SINGLE
YEAR.
>> Michael: 3-0.
THERE'S THE STRIKE.
CLIPS THE OUTSIDE CORNER.
3-1.
>> Paul: HE WAS SO BIG, YOU HIT
HIM.
HE WAS THE PITCHER.
NOW YOU'RE TRYING TO PITCH OUT
OF A TWO OUT JAM.
THAT WALK REALLY COMPLICATED
THINGS FOR C.C.
>> Michael: BASES LOADED.
ONE OUT.
BOTTOM OF THE SECOND.
3-1 COUNT ON HAMILTON.
AND THE PITCH.
GROUNDED AND OFF THE GLOVE OF
TORREYES AND GREGORIUS.
ONE RUN SCORES.
HERE'S THE THROW FROM GARDNER.
PERAZA SCORES AND THE GAME IS
TIED AT TWO.
A TWO-RUN SINGLE FOR HAMILTON
AND WE ARE AT TWO APIECE.
>> Paul: JOE GIRARDI LOOKING AT
THE REPLAY TO SEE IF SANCHEZ
CAUGHT HIM AT THE PLATE.
YOU SEE ROBBY THOMPSON OVER
THERE.
NO, HE'S SAFE.
KIND OF A BAD BREAK FOR C.C.
SABATHIA.
HE KEPT THE BALL ON THE GROUND
RIGHT OFF TORREYES'S GLOVE.
BY GOING BACK GOT BEYOND DIDI
ALSO AND ENDED UP SCORING A
COUPLE RUNS.
BALL GETS IN ON HIM.
THAT BALL'S RIGHT AT HIM.
YOU GOT A CHANCE TO GET AN OUT
AT HOME.
RIGHT OFF THE END OF THE GLOVE.
IT RICOCHETS OFF DIDI INTO LEFT
FIELD.
GETS BY SANCHEZ AND HE TAGGED
HIM BUT HE HAD ALREADY STEPPED
ON THE PLATE.
>> Michael: YANKEE PITCHING
COACH CAME OUT TO TALK WITH
SABATHIA, SETTLE HIM DOWN.
IT'S 2-2 NOW.
STILL JUST ONE OUT.
RUNNERS ON FIRST AND SECOND.
HERE'S ZACK COZART.
AND A STRIKE.
MESORACO HE LEADS OFF SECOND AND
HAMILTON OFF FIRST.
LINED TO LEFT FIELD, IT IS A
BASE HIT.
GARDNER CHARGES.
MESORACO WILL START AT THIRD AND
THE BASES ARE LOADED WITH ONE
OUT FOR JOEY VOTTO.
>> Paul: IF YOU'RE WATCHING
C.C., HE HAS NOT BEEN ABLE TO
BACK UP GOOD QUALITY PITCHES.
HE'LL MAKE ONE GOOD PITCH AND
THEN THE NEXT ONE HE LOSES IT
OUT OVER THE MIDDLE OF THE
PLATE.
YOU SEE COZART GET THE GOOD
PITCHES.
THIS ENDS UP RIGHT DOWN
BROADWAY.
>> Michael: THAT WILL BRING UP
THE DANGEROUS JOEY VOTTO.
A .312 LIFETIME HITTER.
SEE HIS NUMBERS WITH THE BASES
LOAD.
.342.
TWO GRAND SLAMS.
>> Paul: JOEY HAD A LOT OF FIRST
PATCHES LAST NIGHT.
TRY TO WATCH AND JUMP THIS FIRST
PITCH.
>> Michael: HE DID.
HE FOULED IT AWAY.
>> Paul: C.C., A LOT OF TIMES
LEFTIES YOU LOOK FOR THE BALL
OUT OVER THE PLATE.
YOU JUST SEE IT BETTER FROM THE
LEFTY.
THAT BALL KIND OF TWO-SEAMER,
YOU TAIL IN ON THE HANDS.
FOR TOUGH FOR A LEFTY TO HANDLE
THAT PITCH.
>> Michael: THERE'S A STRIKE.
0-2.
>> Paul: WE TALKED ABOUT HIS
INABILITY SO FAR TO THROW AN
AT-BAT QUALITY PITCHES.
THERE'S TWO QUALITY PITCHES.
YOU HAVE AN 0-2 COUNT.
YOU'VE GOT TO BE ABLE TO PUT ONE
OF THE BETTER HITTERS IN THE
NATIONAL LEAGUE AWAY.
VOTTO FROM THE OLD SCHOOL
CHOKING UP A LITTLE BIT.
TWO STRIKES.
BETTER BAT CONTROL.
>> Michael: 1-2.
EVER DO THAT, PAUL?
>> Paul: YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU WERE ALWAYS TAUGHT IN THE
MINOR LEAGUES TO CHOKE UP A
LITTLE BIT WITH TWO STRIKES.
IT REALLY DOES NOT AFFECT THE
POWER TO SQUARE ONE UP.
YOU STILL CAN DRIVE IT.
IT'S JUST A DIFFERENT FEELING.
A LOT OF GUYS EVEN PUT THEIR
PINKIE OVER THE END OF THE BAT
ON THE HANDLE.
A LOT OF TIMES THEY JUST DON'T
FEEL COMFORTABLE.
>> Michael: 2-2.
GROUNDED UP THE MIDDLE AND
THROUGH FOR A BASE HIT.
ONE RUN SCORES.
HERE COMES HAMILTON.
HE'LL SCORE.
COZART MOVES TO THIRD.
IT'S A TWO-RUN SINGLE FOR VOTTO
AND IT'S 4-2 REDS.
>> Paul: I'LL TELL YOU WHAT,
JOEY VOTTO, HIS HIM AT HIS BEST.
HE WENT WITH A CUTTER IN ALSO.
HE GOES WITH ONE AWAY.
HE TRIES TO SINK ONE BACK IN.
JOEY VOTTO JUST DOES NOT GIVE
IN.
GET THAT PITCH AGAIN JUST OUT OF
THE REACH OF CASTRO.
DRIVES IN TWO MORE RUNS.
>> Michael: SO FOR VOTTO, RBI
NUMBER 30 AND 31.
HERE'S ADAM DUVALL.
FIRST AND THIRD WITH ONE OUT.
1-0.
>> Paul: C.C. REALLY LABORING UP
THERE TO TRY TO FIND THAT
CONSISTENCY WITH THAT CUTTER.
HE'S REALLY FALLING IN LOVE AND
PLAYED GOOD WITH.
>> Michael: ANOTHER BASE HITS.
COZART WILL SCORE.
MOVING TO SECOND VOTTO.
IT'S AN RBI SINGLE FOR DUVALL
AND IT'S 5-2 REDS.
>> Paul: WE TALKED IN THE
OPENING, MICHAEL, BOTH THESE
TEAMS HOT OFFENSIVELY.
THIS IS A BALLPARK THAT'S
CONDUCIVE TO GIVING UP A TON OF
RUNS, NOT ONLY WITH HOME RUNS,
BUT BASE HITS.
>> Michael: CHAD GREEN IS UP FOR
THE YANKEES.
THEY CALLED HIM UP BEFORE LAST
NIGHT'S GAME TO GIVE HIM SOME
DEPTH IF THE STARTER DOESN'T GO
LONG.
TANAKA LAST NIGHT GAVE THEM
SEVEN SO THEY DIDN'T NEED GREEN.
THE BULLPEN IS STILL PRETTY
FATIGUED FROM THE 18-INNING GAME
ON SUNDAY NIGHT AT WRIGLEY FIELD
AGAINST THE CUBS.
HERE'S SUAREZ.
>> Paul: HE HAS THE ABILITY TO
COME IN AND THROW 100 PITCHES.
HE CAN GO A LONG WAY.
>> Michael: THERE'S A STRIKE.
0-2 ON SUAREZ.
NINTH BATTER TO COME TO THE
PLATE FOR THE REDS.
RUNNERS ON FIRST AND SECOND.
>> Paul: C.C. HAS NOT HAD A
GREAT INNING, NOT MUCH YOU DO AS
A PITCHER.
EVERY ONCE IN A WHILE YOU
STRUGGLE.
A LOT OF TIMES BALLS ARE HIT
HARD AT PEOPLE.
NOT THIS INNING FOR C.C.
>> Michael: 1-2.
JUST GOT A PIECE TO STAY ALIVE.
>> Paul: CHANGE-UPS IS C.C.'S
FEATURE TONIGHT.
IT WAS JUST UP IN THE STRIKE
ZONE ENOUGH SO SUAREZ COULD GET
A PIECE OF IT.
YOU WANT THAT BALL KIND OF
TAILING AWAY.
>> Michael: 1-2.
2-2.
VOTTO IS AT SECOND.
DUVALL IS AT FIRST.
ONE MAN OUT.
5-2 CINCINNATI.
STILL 2-2.
SCHEBLER STARTED THIS WITH A
SINGLE TO LEFT AND HE IS ON
DECK.
>> Paul: HE JUST NEEDS A BREAK
HERE.
HE'S TRIED THE CHANGE-UP, THE
CURVEBALL, THE CUTTER.
HE'S NOT ABLE TO PUT HIM AWAY.
SUAREZ IS A GOOD SOLID HITTER.
>> Michael: STILL 2-2.
SUAREZ GROUNDED TO THIRD IN THE
FIRST.
HE HAS A FOUR-GAME HITTING
STREAK.
SCHEBLER IS ON DECK.
AND THE PITCH.
SWING AND A MISS.
GOT HIM.
BIG OUT FOR SABATHIA.
>> Paul: FINALLY GOT THAT PITCH.
BACK DOOR CUTTER.
WELL, WITH A RUNNER ON SECOND,
THEY DO NOT SHIFT AS DRASTIC.
LEFTY AGAINST LEFTY.
STRIKE.
AGAIN, STRIKE ONE BUT UP IN THE
STRIKE ZONE.
HE'S TRYING TO GET DOWN AND
AWAY.
>> Michael: GROUND BALL TO
CARTER.
HE BOBBLES.
REGAINS, AND THAT WILL DO IT.
FIVE RUNS ON SIX HITS.
REDS.
WE GO TO THE THIRD.
CINCINNATI'S UP.
SHAPE AND SHAVE ANY LENGTH.
AND BE YOUR BEST YOU
WITH ONEBLADE,
FROM PHILIPS NORELCO.
INNOVATION AND YOU.
PHILIPS NORELCO.
The show's about to start!
How do I look?
Like a bald penguin.
[ laughing ]
Show me the
Billboard Music Awards.
Show me Top Artist.
Show me the
Top Hot 100 Artist.
They give awards for being
hot and 100 years old?
We'll take 2!
[ laughing ]
XFINITY X1 gives you
exclusive access to the best
of the Billboard Music Awards
just by using your voice.
The Billboard Music Awards.
Sunday, May 21st eight
seven central only on ABC.
>> Michael: GIVING UP THE FIVE
RUNS IN THE SECOND THAT DRIVES
UP THE E.R.A. TO 5.13.
PRETTY GOOD NAMES ABOVE HIM.
TREVOR BAUER OF THE INDIANS,
7.36 AND COSTNER OF THE ORIOLES,
6.63.
STRIKE.
C.C. HAS ALWAYS FANCIED HIMSELF
A GOOD HITTER.
THREE HOMERS, 15 RBIs.
3-1 ON C.C.
SO ADLEMAN'S TEAM HAS PICKED HIM
UP WITH FIVE RUNS.
AND HE HAS A 3-2 COUNT ON THE
OPPOSING PITCHER.
>> Paul: ADLEMAN HAS THAT LITTLE
HESITATION.
YOU TALKED ABOUT HIS FASTBALL
PLAYING A LITTLE HARDER.
KIND OF HOLD ON TO IT AND JUMP
AT YOU AS A HITTER.
>> Michael: BRYAN BRYCE SAID
TODAY AND YOU SEE WHAT HE'S DONE
AT GREAT AMERICAN, 4 FOR 10, HIS
FASTBALL MIGHT BE 91 OR 92 AND
PLAYS MUCH HIGHER.
SABATHIA WALKS.
THAT'S THE LAST THING ADLEMAN
WANTED TO DO.
WHAT DO THEY MEAN BY THAT BALL?
IS IT THE WAY IT'S COMING OUT OF
HIS HAND OR HE CHANGES HIS
SPEED?
>> Paul: IT'S BECAUSE OF THE
DECEPTION AND THE HITTER, YOU
SEE THAT HESITATION.
YOU JUST DON'T QUITE PICK UP THE
BALL AND YOU HAVE A LOT OF THE
OFF SPEED STUFF WITH IT.
THERE'S KIND OF A HESITATION.
ONCE YOU KIND OF MOVE AS A
HITTER, YOU GO THROUGH YOUR
RHYTHM AND IT KIND OF SETS YOU
OFF.
>> Michael: SABATHIA ON FIRST.
>> Paul: C.C. DOESN'T LOOK LIKE
YOUR TYPICAL BASE STEALER.
>> Michael: I'D BE SHOCKED IF HE
GOES.
>> Paul: YEAH.
>> Michael: HERE'S GARDNER.
1-0.
GARDNER IN AN 11-GAME HITTING
STREAK.
FOULED OUT TO SUAREZ TO START
THE GAME.
HE IS 6 FOR 20 ON THIS ROAD
TOWNSHIP, BUT THE ONLY HIT HE
HAD WAS IN THE NINTH INNING
AGAINST THE CUBS ON FRIDAY, IT
WOULD BE A GOOD ROAD TRIP FOR
HIM.
GAVE THE YANKEES A WIN.
THEY ENDED UP SWEEPING THE CUBS.
1-0.
1-1.
>> Paul: MICHAEL, YOU WERE UP
THERE ON THE WEEKEND.
DO PEOPLE COME DOWN YET IN
CHICAGO FROM THE WORLD?
>> Michael: NO.
>> Paul: THAT'S ALL THAT'S ON
THEIR MIND.
>> Michael: WELL, THEY HAD 108
YEARS TO WAIT.
>> Paul: THAT'S ALL.
>> Michael: 1-1.
ALONG WITH PAUL O'NEAL, I'M
MICHAEL CANE.
HERE AT THE GREAT AMERICAN
BALLPARK IN CINCINNATI.
A PLACE THAT GUARD HER HAS FOND
MEMORIES OF.
FROM HIS ALL-STAR GAME.
HE SAID HE WILL NEVER EVER
FORGET THAT.
>> Paul: CHANGE-UP RIGHT OFF THE
OUTSIDE CORNER.
BACK-TO-BACK CHANGE-UPS.
HE KIND OF TURNS THAT OVER.
ALMOST GOT LIKE A SCREWBALL
ACTION TO IT.
WHICH ALLOWS HIM TO PITCH
LEFTIES IN WITH THE HARD STUFF
AND THEN TURN THAT CHANGE-UP
AWAY.
>> Michael: 1-2.
2-2 ADLEMAN A NATIVE OF STATTON
ISLAND IN NEW YORK.
CALLED UP EARLIER THAN THEY WERE
GOING TO WITH THE INJURY TO
FINNEGAN.
WE MENTIONED EARLIER THE REDS
HAVE THREE OF THEIR FIVE
PROJECTED STARTING PITCHERS ON
DL WHICH MAKES THEIR START ALL
THE MORE AMAZING.
GROUND BALL TO SHORT.
THIS COULD BE TWO.
THERE'S ONE.
ON TO FIRST.
THEY GET HIM.
A DOUBLE PLAY!
6-4-3 AS GARDNER HIT THE BALL
HARD.
PERHAPS TOO HARD.
BUT THE YANKEES MIGHT CHALLENGE.
>> Paul: THIS IS AWFUL CLOSE AT
FIRST.
WE'LL GET A BETTER LOOK AT IT
HERE.
>> Michael: LOOKS LIKE THEY GOT
HIM.
GOOD CALL BY THE UMPIRE.
CREW CHIEF BARRETT.
THERE'S GARRY SANCHEZ.
WENT DEEP AND LEFT IN THE FIRST
INNING.
YANKEES ARE DOWN 5-2.
WE'RE IN THE TOP OF THE THIRD
INNING.
>> Michael: FAIR BALL.
FIRES ACROSS THE DIAMOND AND
GETS SANCHEZ FOR THE FINAL OUT.
NO RUNS.
NO HITS.
NO ERRORS.
NOBODY LEFT ON BASE.
Nobody does
underwater stunts, Sylvia.
Except me, of course.
This is my stop.
Adios!
♪  ♪
If you're a stuntman,
you cheat death.
It's what you do.
If you want to save
fifteen percent
or more on car insurance,
you switch to GEICO.
It's what you do.
Número uno!
Every team has a goal.
Every team makes a plan.
But only one team in the world
has what it takes to succeed
no matter what
gets in their way.
Find out more at
goarmy.com/team
>> Michael: CINCINNATI REDS 5,
NEW YORK YANKEES 2.
BOTTOM THE THIRD INNING HERE AT
GREAT AMERICAN BALLPARK.
HE'LL FACE THE BOTTOM THIRD OF
THE ORDER.
PERAZA HAD A SINGLE RUN IN LEFT
FOR CINCINNATI.
POPPED UP.
CASTRO IS THERE TO MAKE THE
PLAY.
ONE AWAY.
SATURDAY THE ONLY PLACE TO SEE
NASCAR IS ON FS1 AS THE MONSTER
MG SERIES GOES TO KANSAS.
THE GREEN FLAG DROPS AT 7:00
EASTERN ONLY ON FS1.
HERE'S MEZ MESORACO WHO WALKED
AND SCORED IN THE SECOND INNING.
THEY SHIFT FOR HIM.
THREE INFIELDERS ON THE LEFT
SIDE.
INSIDE, 1-0.
IN TALKING TO BRYAN PRICE TODAY
HE SAID I TOLD MY TEAM IN SPRING
TRAINING DON'T LISTEN TO THE
OUTSIDE NOISE.
EVERYBODY SAYS WE'RE NOT GOING
TO BE A GOOD TEAM.
YOU HAVE TO BELIEVE THAT WE ARE
GOING TO BE A GOOD TEAM.
WHAT WE BELIEVE IS THE ONLY
THING THAT COUNTS.
GROUND BALL TO THIRD.
TORREYES.
FOR A SECOND OUT.
PART OF THEIR SUCCESS AND THE
THING THAT HE'S THE MOST PROUD
OF IS HIS OFFENSE.
FIFTH IN BATTING AVERAGE IN
MAJOR LEAGUE.
TIED FOR SECOND IN EXTRA BASE
HITS.
SIXTH IN HOME RUNS.
THIRD IN RUNS PER GAME.
36 IN STOLEN BASES.
SO THEY DO IT ALL, SPEED AND
POWER.
HOW DIFFICULT IS IT TO SHUT OUT
THE NOISE THAT THEY'RE NOT A
GOOD TEAM?
THEY WON ONLY 68 GAMES LAST
YEAR.
>> Paul: IT'S NOT REALLY THE
FANS.
IT'S REALLY YOU WHAT NBL THE
CLUBHOUSE.
THERE'S GOT TO BE SOME KIND OF
LEADERSHIP OF PLAYERS.
THEY HAVE NOT HAD THAT CULTURE
HERE IN A WHILE TO BE A WINNING
TEAM.
THAT SOMETIMES CAN BE A PROBLEM.
BUT UNTIL YOU GO OUT AND SHOW,
HEY, YOU KNOW, WE CAN WIN SOME
GAMES, IT'S VERY EASY TO SAY
YEAH, WE'RE GOING TO WIN GAMES
AND TRULY NOT BELIEVE THEM.
>> ADLEMAN WITH A GROUND BALL TO
CASTRO.
C.C. BOUNCES BACK WITH A ONE,
TWO, THREE INNING.
HERE IN THE THIRD.
THREE IN THE BOOK IN CINCINNATI.
THE REDS LEAD THE YANKS 5-2.
[ Birds Chirping ]
[ Inhales, Exhales ]
[ Announcer ] Cigarettes
are not just dangerous
when they're smoked.
[ Rat Squeaking ]
They're dangerous long after.
Cigarette butts are toxic.
They release chemicals
that poison our water...
and harm wildlife.
And millions...
are polluting our environment.
[ Sniffing ]
[ Seagulls Squawking ]
>> Michael: WE ANY TO THE
FOURTH.
REDS LEAD THE YANKEES.
YOU GREW UP IN COLUMBUS, YOU
MADE IT WITH THE REDS, AND YOU
WON A CHAMPIONSHIP IN 1990.
>> Paul: AND THE LAST
CHAMPIONSHIP THE REDS HAVE WON.
FUN YEAR.
YOU TALKED ABOUT CUTTING OUT THE
NOISE.
THAT WAS ONE OF THE YEARS COMING
INTO THIS SEASON THAT NOBODY
EXPECTED US TO WIN.
OBVIOUSLY GOING INTO THE WORLD
SERIES --
>> Michael: CASTRO RIPS ONE OVER
THE HEAD OF DUVALL AND HAD GOES
TO THE WALL.
CASTRO WILL GET HIMSELF A
DOUBLE.
GO QUICKLY TO CHRIS MYERS IN
L.A.
>> THE NATIONALS IN BALTIMORE
AND DANIEL MURPHY WITH HIS SIXTH
HOME RUN OF THE SEASON TO GET
THE NATIONALS ON THE BOARD.
HAS THAT LEAD.
IT'S 1-0 WASHINGTON IN THE
FIFTH.
LET'S GO BACK TO CINCINNATI WITH
PAUL AND MIKE.
>> Michael: BACK HERE AT GREAT
AMERICAN BALLPARK.
WE THANK CHRIS.
A DOUBLE FOR CASTRO AND
ELLSBURY.
YANKEES TRAIL 5-2, TOP OF THE
FOURTH INNING.
YOU TALKED WITH THAT 1990 TEAM.
>> Paul: I DID UNTIL HE HUT THAT
BULLET OFF THE WALL.
YOU COME OUT OF SPRING TRAINING.
HAVE A GREAT YEAR.
PLAY THE MIGHTY OAKLAND A'S.
IT'S WHAT THE PEOPLE BELIEVE.
ALL OF A SUDDEN FOUR GAMES LATER
YOU'RE WORLD CHAMPIONS.
IT DOESN'T SINK IN FOR A WHILE.
BUT IT TAKES A LOT.
WHEN THE BULLPENS OF BASEBALL IN
MY MIND CHANGED WITH RANDY
MYERS, NORM CHARLTON, ROB .563.
FOR THE A'S, HIT .207.
>> Paul: THE FUNNY THING, NOT
FUNNY, BUT ERIC DAVIS WHO WAS
OUR BEST PLAYER AT THE TIME WAS
INJURED IN GAME FOUR.
GAME FOUR IS A COMPLETELY
DIFFERENT THEORY COMING BACK
OUT.
BUT THE WHOLE POINT OF THE STORY
WAS THAT'S POP OF THOSE YEARS
YOU WERE TALKING ABOUT THE REDS
UNTIL YOU BELIEVE THIS AND THAT.
JUST COMING OUT OF SPRING
TRAINING, YOU KNOW, YOU KNEW YOU
WERE A DECENT TEAM, BUT DO YOU
BELIEVE YOU'RE GOING TO WIN A
WORLD SERIES UNTIL YOU DO IT.
YOU REALLY DON'T.
>> Michael: COUNT 1-2 STILL ON
ELLSBURY.
FLY BALL TO LEFT IN THE FIRST
INNING.
YOU GREW UP GOING TO A REDS
GAME.
>> Paul: I GREW UP IN COLUMBUS,
OHIO.
THAT WAS OUR SUMMER VACATION,
DRIVING DOWN TO WATCH PETE ROSE,
ROBERTO CLEMENTE.
>> Michael: 1-2.
ELLSBURY BACK.
>> Paul: SHOWS YOU HOW LONG AGO
THAT IS.
THAT'S THREE FIELDS AGO.
>> Michael: YOU REMEMBER THIS,
PAUL?
WAS IT LIKE YESTERDAY?
>> Paul: YEAH.
I SHOULD HAVE CALLEDS BENZINGER
OFF.
I WAS OUT HERE CRUISING AROUND.
THAT LAST OUT, THERE'S NOTHING
LIKE IT.
NOTHING ELSE TO PROVE.
>> Michael: YOU HAD THAT FEELING
FIVE TIMES IN YOUR CAREER.
PRETTY COOL.
FOUR WITH THE YANKEES AND ONE
WITH THE REDS.
1-2.
JUST MISSED THAT ONE.
2-2.
>> Paul: WE TALKED ABOUT C.C.
NOT HAVING THAT, BUT YOU SEE HIS
CHANGE-UP.
ABLE TO THROW IT IN AND OUT.
TRY TO RUN THIS ONE BACK OVER
THE INSIDE CORNER.
DIDN'T QUITE CATCH IT.
>> Michael: 3-2.
ON DECK FOR THE YANKEES AARON
JUDGE.
YANKEES ARE DOWN 5-2.
LEADOFF DOUBLE BY CASTRO.
AND THE 3-2.
HE WALKED HIM.
SO THIS IS A BIG SPOT FOR AARON
JUDGE AS HE COMES UP AS THE
TYING RUN HERE IN THE FOURTH
INNING.
AND JUDGE STRUCK OUT IN THE
SECOND INNING.
>> Paul: AARON JUDGE PUT A LOT
OF NUMBERS UP ON THE BOARD IN A
HURRY.
IN HIS DEMEANOR, HUMBLE, BIG.
REALLY A NICE KID.
HE JUST -- YOU LOVE TO SEE KIDS
LIKE THIS DO WELL.
LAST YEAR HE WENT THROUGH SOME
STRUGGLES.
HE'S REALLY MADE SOME GOOD
ADJUSTMENTS SO FAR THIS YEAR.
IT'S REALLY PAID OFF.
>> Michael: LAST YEAR HE STRUCK
OUT 44% OF HIS PLATE
APPEARANCES.
THIS YEAR 26%.
18 POINT DROP IS THE BEST IN THE
MAJOR LEAGUE, SO HE COVERED UP
SOME OF THE HOLES.
BROKEN BAT.
SLOW OVER TO SHORT.
THEY GET ONE ON THE FIRST.
MOVING TO THIRD IS CASTRO.
SO A 6-4-3 DOUBLE PLAYOFF THE
BAT OF JUDGE.
>> Paul: THIS IS THE WAY YOU
WANT TO PITCH BIG GUYS.
THEY WANT TO GET THEIR ARMS
EXTENDED.
YOU SEE THIS BALL GETS IN.
JAM ITS.
GETS DOUBLE PLAY.
THIS DOESN'T QUITE GET OUT AND
ALL OF A SUDDEN, A BIG HITTER,
IT'S IMPORTANT TO GET YOUR HANDS
OUT.
GET EXTENSIONS.
THAT'S WHERE YOU DRIVE THE BALL.
IT GETS TIED UP LIKE THAT ON A
GOOD PITCH.
>> Michael: BROKEN BAT.
LOOPER INTO RIGHT FIELD.
SCORING IS CASTRO.
AN RBI SINGLE FOR GREGORIUS AND
NOW THE REDS LEAD 5-3.
>> Paul: THOSE ARE BIG HITS.
THOSE ARE THE ONES THAT COME
BACK TO HAUNT THE PITCHERS.
GOT IN ON DIDI'S HANDS.
DUNK IT INTO RIGHT FIELD.
>> Michael: HIT A HOME RUN IN
HIS FIRST AT-BAT.
HERE'S CHRIS CARTER WITH
GREGORIUS ON FIRST.
>> Paul: THERE MIGHT BE A FEW
RUNS SCORED HERE TONIGHT,
MICHAEL, HUH?
>> Michael: ALTHOUGH IT'S NOT
WARM.
>> Paul: YOU HIT IT ON THE
BARREL, BROKEN BATS ARE FALLING
IN.
GROUND BALLS ARE GOING THROUGH.
>> Michael: THIS IS A HITTER'S
BALL CLUB.
>> Paul: NO DOUBT.
CARTER FOULS AWAY.
HERE'S A 1-1 TO CARTER.
AGAIN, FOULED BACK.
>> Paul: HE'S A HOME RUN HITTER
IF YOU LOOK AT CARTER'S STATS
FROM LAST YEAR.
41 HOME RUNS.
200 SOME STRIKEOUTS.
AREN'T A LOT OF AT-BATS.
SOONER OR LATER YOU'RE GOING TO
HIT SOME.
HE HASN'T HAD A TON OF AT-BATS
THIS YEAR.
HE'S GOING TO STRIKE OUT, BUT HE
NEEDS A LOT OF AT-BATS TO MAKE
UP THOSE HOME RUNS AND HAS NOT
BEEN ABLE TO GET THEM AT THIS
POINT.
>> Michael: ALSO YOU WOULD THINK
IF HE DOESN'T GET A LOT OF
AT-BATS AND PLAYING TIME IT'S
HARD TO KEEP YOUR RHYTHM AS A
HITTER.
>> Paul: PRETTY MUCH TO MY
POINT.
HE'S HAD A COUPLE GOOD PITCHES
TO HIT AT THIS AT-BAT, BUT WHEN
YOU FOUL THEM OFF AND EVERYTHING
IS NOT GOING WELL AND YOU'RE
WANT USED TO PLAYING EVERY DAY.
>> Michael: TWO BALLS, TWO
STRIKES, TWO OUT.
YANKEES DOWN BY TWO.
PAYING A LOT OF ATTENTION TO
GREGORIUS.
RUNNER GOES.
SWUNG AND MISSED AND CARTER DOWN
ON STRIKES.
BUT THE YANKEES GET A RUN ON TWO
HITS.
ONE MAN LEFT ON BASE.
GO TO THE BOTTOM OF THE FOURTH.
5-3 REDS.
(brakes squeal)
Ahhhh...you do know the
experts at Midas
will tell you what needs
fixing now
and what can wait, right?
Like...I don't know...brakes.
Of course I do.
(brakes continue squealing)
Get up to a hundred dollars back
on a two-axle brake service
with your Midas Credit Card...
now at Midas.
Z2BJDZ ZVPZ
Y2BJDY YVPY
A naturally aspirated
5.0-liter V8 engine.
A 10-speed Direct-Shift
transmission.
A meticulously
crafted interior.
All of these are feats
of engineering.
Combining them with
near-perfect weight
distribution...
...is a feat of amazing.
Experience the first-ever
471-horsepower
Lexus LC 500
or the Multistage
Hybrid LC 500h.
Experience Amazing.
>> Michael: BACK HERE AT
CINCINNATI REDS LEAD THE YANKEES
5-3 BOTTOM OF THE FOURTH INNING.
0-1.
>> Paul: GARY SANCHEZ TRYING TO
GO TO ANOTHER PITCH AND LET HIM
OFF WITH A CHANGE-UP TO TRY TO
FIND SOME RHYTHM, SOME PITCH
THAT HE CAN COUNT ON.
ANOTHER CHANGE-UP.
>> Michael: HAMILTON HAD A BIG
HIT IN THAT SECOND INNING.
TWO-RUN SINGLE.
THE FIRST HE GROUND TO SHORT.
HE'S 1 FOR 2.
AND THE 0-2 PITCH.
1-2.
RIGHT AT CASTRO.
ONE AWAY.
NEXT ON FS1, AFTER ALL THE
ACTION TO THE DIAMOND, THE BEST
TEAM OF ANALYSTS IN BASEBALL GET
YOU CAUGHT UP ON A FULL NIGHT OF
ACTION IN THE BIG LEAGUE ON "MLB
WHIPAROUND" NEXT ON FS1.
WATCH IS LIVE ON FOX SPORTS GO.
>> Paul: A LOT OF OFFENSE ON
THAT SCREEN RIGHT THERE,
MICHAEL.
MACHADO, HARPER, BRYANT.
THE STARS OF TODAY.
>> Michael: IF YOU HAD TO START
A TEAM, WHICH ONE WILL YOU START
WITH?
>> Paul: MY KIDS HAVE ASKED ME
THE SAME THING AND I HAVE TO GO
WITH MACHADO.
I TELL YOU WHY.
IT'S BECAUSE YOU TAKE THE BEST
OUTFIELDER AND THE DIFFERENCE IN
THE NUMBERS OF THE MOST
UNBELIEVABLE MIKE TROUT
OUTFIELDER TO A GOOD OUTFIELDER
IS, YOU KNOW, THIS MUCH.
BUT YOU TAKE MANNY MACHADO AND
PUT HIM AT SHORT OR THIRD AND
THE DIFFERENCE IN HIS OFFENSIVE
NUMBERS IS MUCH GREATER THAN AN
OFFENSE TO TROUT.
HE DOES SO MANY THINGS IN THE
GAME.
>> Michael: I'VE GOT GARRY
SANCHEZ TWICE FOR THE HOME PLATE
UMPIRE GIVING HIM TIME TO SHAKE
IT OFF.
OUCH.
AND THE 0-2.
>> Paul: YOU AGREE WITH ME
THERE?
>> Michael: I SEE WHAT YOU'RE
SAYING.
OBVIOUSLY, TROUT SCORE IS ALWAYS
HIGHER THAN MACHADO.
HIGH FLY BALL, CENTER FIELD.
ELLSBURY DRIFTS BACK.
HE MAKES THE PLAY FOR THE SECOND
OUT.
THAT WILL BRING UP VOTTO WHO HAD
A TWO-RUN SINGLE IN THE SECOND.
I GAVE YOU HIS CAREER NUMBERS.
.312 BATTING AVERAGE.
.424 ON BASE.
FIVE OTHER PLAYERS HAVE .310
TO .530 OR BETTER AND 5,000 OR
MORE PLATE APPEARANCES.
BABY RUTH, LOU GEHRIG.
HIS ON-BASE PERCENTAGE, TEN BEST
ALL TIME WITH A MINIMUM OF 5,000
PLATE APPEARANCES.
AND HE'S MAKING A CASE FF A HALL
OF FAME CAREER.
>> Paul: IT'S ABOUT HIS
APPROACH.
YOU SEE A LOT OF PITCHERS, A LOT
OF HITTERS CHANGE THEIR
APPROACH.
CHANCES ARE THE PITCHER'S GOT
YOU WHERE HE WANTS YOU.
YOU STICK WITH WHAT YOU'RE
TRYING TO DO, YOU STAND A MUCH
BETTER CHANCE.
>> Michael: HE IDOLIZED TED
WILLIAMS GROWING UP AS A KID AND
READ ALL OF WILLIAMS BOOKS.
MESMERIZED BY HIM.
BUT IN HIS BIG LEAGUE CAREER HE
SAID THE PLAYER HE LEARNED THE
MOST FROM, SCOTT ROWLAND.
TOLD HIM HOW TO BE A BIG LEAGUE,
HOW TO CONDUCT HIMSELF, HOW TO
PLAY THE GAME THE RIGHT WAY.
AND A PROUD CANADIAN AS WELL.
SO VOTTO IS FOURTH ON THE
CANADIAN BORN PLAYER HOME RUN
LIST.
LARRY WALKER IS FIRST.
JASON BAY.
>> Paul: THREE OF THOSE GUYS
MVP.
>> Michael: BOTTOM ONE IN 2010.
AFTER FINISHING SECOND IN ROOKIE
OF THE YEAR IN 2009.
3-2.
HIGH FLY BALL, LEFT CENTER.
ELLSBURY THERE TO MAKE THE PLAY
AND THE REDS GO DOWN IN ORDER
AGAINST SABATHIA WHO IS RETIRING
EIGHT IN A ROW.
♪♪
Where did we find the
inspiration for our new flavors?
It walked right in the door.
Introducing new Signature
Crafted Recipes.
Pico Guacamole.
Sweet Barbecue Bacon.
Maple Bacon Dijon.
Get a free medium Fries and soft
drink in the McDonald's App with
purchase of any Signature
Crafted Recipe sandwich.
You bring your flavor to the
world.
We bring ours to you.
WiFi.
We literally cannot
live without it.
And if we can't live without it,
maybe it's time to reimagine
it and make it even better.
So it's awesomely fast.
No. Still nope.
Now we're talking.
So it works here
and here and here.
And so you can even take
the occasional time out.
Nooooooo!
Yes!!!
Yes, indeed.
Speed, coverage, control.
Introducing Xfinity xFi.
Find your awesome and
change the way you WiFi.
>> Michael: WELCOME BACK TO
GREAT AMERICAN BALLPARK.
NOW TO THE FIFTH INNING.
5-3 REDS.
RONALD TORREYES LEADS OFF.
SABATHIA SEEMS AS IF HE'S
SETTLED DOWN AS HE IS ON DECK.
YANKEES DON'T SEEM LIKE THEY
HAVE ANY INTENTION OF
PINCH-HITTING FOR HIM.
TORREYES GROUNDED TO SHORT IN
THE SECOND INNING.
5-6-0 FOR THE REDS.
3-6-1 FOR THE YANKEES.
>> Paul: I WAS WATCHING C.C.
COME OFF THE MOUND.
HE'S A VETERAN PITCHER SAYING I
NEED THESE PITCHES.
I DO REMEMBER ONE PITCH VERY
CLOSE.
>> Michael: THERE'S A STRIKE.
>> Paul: SAYING I NEED THESE
PITCHES.
I'M STRUGGLING OUT HERE.
I NEED SOME OF THESE CLOSE
PITCHES.
>> Michael: 2-2.
YANKEES HAVE WON SIX IN A ROW.
REDS HAVE ONE FIVE OF SIX.
2-2.
3-2.
AN IMPORTANT BATTER IN THE
NATIONAL LEAGUE IF HE CAN GET
ON.
SABATHIA CAN BUNT.
AND STRIKE THREE, TORREYES DOWN
LOOKING.
BACK TO CHRIS MYERS.
>> MICHAEL, THE RED SOX IN MALL,
13th HOME RUN OF THE SEASON.
A FIVE-RUN FIRST FOR MILWAUKEE.
SO THAMES TIES AARON JUDGE.
5-1 GAME IN THE THIRD.
BACK TO CINCINNATI.
>> Michael: THANK YOU, CHRIS.
C.C. SABATHIA STEPS UP WITH ONE
OUT.
AND HE'LL TAKE A STRIKE.
AND TORREYES DID NOT LIKE THIS
CALL.
>> Paul: AGAIN, A COUPLE LOW
STRIKES HAVE BEEN CALLED
TONIGHT.
THE PITCH BEFORE THAT BORDERLINE
OFF HIS TOE RIGHT THERE.
>> Michael: SO IF HE'S THAT HE
SWUNG AND THE SWING SUPERSEDES,
SO C.C. WILL HAVE TO GET BACK IN
THE BOX.
JOE SAYS WHY DON'T YOU CHECK
WITH THE THIRD BASE UMPIRE.
THAT'S HIS COMPLAINT.
>> Paul: CHECK THIS OUT.
THAT'S PROBABLY A SWING, BUT AS
A HITTER, THE LAST THING ON YOUR
MIND, YOU FEEL LIKE YOU CHECK
AND THEN YOU FEEL YOUR BIG TOE
STARTS THROBBING, IT'S TIME TO
GO TO FIRST BASE.
>> Michael: ADLEMAN FEELS THE
1-2.
SABATHIA DOWN ON STRIKES.
>> Paul: THAT WAS IT RIGHT
THERE, JAMES.
WE WERE TALKING ABOUT IT.
A YANKEE PITCHER, C.C. HAS THREE
HOME RUNS, HAS NOT HIT A HOME
RUN.
SO OBVIOUSLY C.C. DIDN'T HIT ANY
HOME RUNS WITH THE YANKEES.
WHAT WAS IT, 1972?
>> Michael: 1973.
>> Paul: A NEW YORK YANKEE
PITCHER HAS NOT HIT A HOME RUN.
NICE LITTLE BREAKING BALL THERE.
>> Michael: HERE'S BRETT
GARDNER.
HE'S 0 FOR 2.
AND A STRIKE.
>> Paul: ADLEMAN HAS GONE TO THE
BREAKING BALL THIS INNING.
C.C. WENT TO THE CHANGE-UP LAST
INNING.
ADLEMAN GOES TO THE BREAKING
BALL AWAY FROM THE CHANGE-UP.
WE CAN DO THAT.
>> Michael: THE TWO OF US
TOGETHER?
>> Paul: YEAH.
TOM SAWYER STYLE.
>> Michael: PUSH BUNT.
COULD BE A TOUGH PLAY.
GOOD BUNT.
AND A BASE HIT FOR GARDNER.
SO THAT EXTENDS HIS HITTING
STREAK TO 12 STRAIGHT.
>> Paul: THIS IS WHAT YOU WANT
TO SEE.
GARDNER, HE'S KIND OF LEARNING
ON THE JOB.
HE'S ALWAYS BEEN A GOOD ENOUGH
HITTER WHERE HE DIDN'T HAVE TO
DO THIS.
AT THE MAJOR LEAGUE LEVEL WITH
HIS SPEED, IT'S ANOTHER THING HE
CAN DO.
BUT EVERY TIME THAT, YOU KNOW,
YOU DON'T DO IT WELL, YOU THINK
WHAT WOULD HAVE HAPPENED IF I
WOULD HAVE SWUNG THE BAT.
THESE ARE THE ONES THEY CAN
CONDITION TO WORK ON.
>> Michael: AND THAT'S GOING TO
BRING A TRIP TO THE MOUND FROM
MACK JENKINS.
WITH THAT BUNT A 12-GAME HITTING
STREAK.
MIKE TROUT HAS THE LONGEST IN
BASEBALL.
AND BRETT HAS JUST BROKEN THE
TIE WITH BOGAERTS OF THE RED
SOX.
>> Paul: LAST NIGHT HE WAS ON
THE VERGE OF LOSING IT AND HE
HIT AN ABSOLUTE BOMB.
TONIGHT HE BREAKS IT AGAIN WITH
A DRAG BUNT.
>> Michael: THERE'S THE PITCH
COUNT FOR ADLEMAN.
78 PITCHES.
WE WANT TO GIVE THE LAST YANKEE
PITCHER THAT HIT THE HOME RUN
WAS LINDSEY McDANIEL IN 1972.
THAT'S THE SIXTH TO LAST GAME
BEFORE THE DH.
HERE'S GARRY SANCHEZ.
HE'S HIT SOME HOME RUNS.
SANCHEZ WITH A LONG HOME RUN IN
THE FIRST INNING.
GROUNDED TO THIRD IN THE THIRD.
WE'RE IN THE FIFTH.
IT'S 5-3 REDS.
LORENZEN IS IN THE BULLPEN FOR
THE REDS.
NOW, PAUL, YOU KNOW WHAT LINDSEY
McDANIEL IS FAMOUS FOR IN YANKEE
HISTORY OTHER THAN THE LAST HOME
RUN?
>> Paul: NO.
>> Michael: HE WAS TRADED FOR
YOUR FORMER MANAGER, LOU
PINELLA.
THAT WAS THE WINTER OF 1973.
OUCH.
I BELIEVE THAT GOT MESORACO.
IT DID.
>> Paul: YOU SEE YOUR FOLD OUT
FRONT SO YOUR EXTENSION ON THE
BACK SIDE IS A LITTLE LONG.
TANGLED WITH WITH HIS MASK.
TWO BALLS, TWO STRIKES.
TWO OUTS.
ONE MAN ON.
YANKEES DOWN BY TWO, TOP OF THE
FIFTH.
RUNNER GOES.
SWING AND A MISS.
AND HE GETS HIT AGAIN AS SANCHEZ
DOWN ON STRIKES.
AFTER FOUR AND A HALF, HALFWAY
THROUGH.
REDS UP BY TWO.
Hey curly-haired man!
Hey.
You're going to want to sit down
for this.
Because you can get a large
2-topping Pizza Hut pizza
for $7.99 delivered.
And with the new Pizza Hut
delivery tracker,
we'll text you when your order
is on the way.
The best pizza delivery deal.
Now easier to track.
It's not easy to brew a beer
this easy to drink.
Bud Light is tasted
by brewmasters
every step of the process.
It's a tough job,
but for you and your friends,
it's worth it.
We don't just brew beer.
We brew beer for friends.
Type 2 diabetes, listen up.
We're not professional athletes.
But that doesn't
mean we're giving up.
I'm in this for me.
For me.
Along with diet and exercise,
FARXIGA helps
lower blood sugar
in adults with type 2 diabetes.
Lowering A1C by
up to 1.2 points.
Do not take if
allergic to FARXIGA.
If you experience symptoms of
a serious allergic reaction
such as rash, swelling,
difficulty breathing
or swallowing,
stop taking and seek
medical help right away.
Do not take FARXIGA if you
have severe kidney problems,
are on dialysis, or
have bladder cancer.
Tell your doctor right away
if you have blood or
red color in your urine
or pain while you urinate.
FARXIGA can cause
serious side effects
including dehydration,
genital yeast infections
in women and men,
serious urinary
tract infections,
low blood sugar,
and kidney problems.
Stop taking FARXIGA and call
your doctor right away
if you have signs
of ketoacidosis,
which is serious and
may lead to death.
I'm in this for my family.
I'm in this for me.
Ask your doctor about FARXIGA
and learn how you can
get it for FREE.
If you can't afford
your medication,
AstraZeneca may be able to help.
♪ The only thing ♪
♪ that I was missing ♪
♪ was on that cheek ♪
♪ that I was kissing. ♪
♪ ♪
♪ We do it 'cause it
feels good. ♪
feels... ♪
.
>> Michael: ADLEMAN'S NIGHT
LIKELY OVER.
>> Paul: NOT USUALLY HOW YOU END
AN INNING.
GOOD NIGHT.
WE'LL SEE YOU.
>> Michael: WE START THE BOTTOM
OF THE FIFTH.
CINCINNATI 5, NEW YORK YANKEES
3.
>> Paul: WE TALKED IN THE
PREGAME A LITTLE BIT ABOUT IT.
THIS IS PRICE'S IDEAL SITUATION
WHERE HE GETS THROUGH THE FIVE
INNINGS WITH THE LEAD.
VERY HAPPY WITH HIS BULLPEN.
BULLPEN'S BEEN PRETTY SUCCESSFUL
SO FAR THIS YEAR.
2-1.
DUVALL'S 1 FOR 2, RBI SINGLE IN
THE SECOND INNING.
GROUND BALL TO SHORT.
GREGORIUS.
ONE AWAY.
FS1 SPONSORED BY "ALIEN
COVENANT."
AND BY FALKEN TIRE, THE OFFICIAL
TIRE OF MAJOR LEAGUE BASEBALL.
HERE YOU ON EUGENIO SUAREZ.
A GROUND BALL TO TWO AND A
STRIKEOUT.
CASTRO PLAYS HIM UP THE MIDDLE.
AND A GROUND BALL TO GREGORIUS.
TWO AWAY.
>> Paul: A LOT OF TIMES WHEN YOU
LOOK AT CATCHERS WHO GET HIT,
THEY DON'T SHOW A LOT OF EMOTION
BECAUSE A LOT OF TIMES IT'S
THEIR FAULT.
WATCH MESORACO AS HE GOES
FORWARD.
A LOT OF TIMES IF CATCHERS REACH
FOR THE BALL, SAME THING.
AS YOU GO FORWARD, YOU'RE
GETTING CLOSER TO THAT BATTER.
YOU SAW NO EMOTION WHATSOEVER.
HE JUST WALKS AWAY.
NOT YOU THAT WANT IT TO HAPPEN.
AS A CATCHER YOUR REACTION TO IS
TO REACH FOR THE BALL OR GO
FORWARD AND CAUSE THAT BACKSWING
TO HIT YOU.
SCHEBLER FOULS OFF THE FIRST
PITCH.
NICE CATCH IN THE STANDS.
AND THAT HIT SCHEBLER, SO HE
WILL TAKE FIRST.
>> Paul: AGAIN, C.C., A LOT OF
HIS SUCCESS AGAINST LEFTIES IS
BEING ABLE TO THROW THAT
FASTBALL IN.
TONIGHT YOU SEE THAT BALL KIND
OF GOING IN.
JUST CANNOT CONTROL THAT INNER
HALF.
MICHAEL, AS YOU WERE GOING
THROUGH THE READ, I LOOKED UP.
I THINK I SAW THE MOON.
>> Michael: AND IT WENT AWAY.
>> Paul: THE MOON AND THE SUN
HAVE NOT LIVED IN THE MIDWEST
FOR THE LAST COUPLE WEEKS.
>> Michael: RUNNER GOES.
INTO SECOND FIELD, BUT SCHEBLER
WILL STAY PUT WITH THE STOLEN
BASE.
I TOLD YOU THIS REDS TEAM WILL
RUN.
>> Paul: JUST BACK, BUT IF YOU
LOOK AT HIS RELEASE POINT HERE,
HE'S SO GOOD, SO QUICK WITH HIS
FEET.
HE JUST DOES NOT GET A GOOD GRIP
AND THE BALL JUST SAILS.
>> Michael: FLY BALL, FAIRLY
DEEP LEFT, GOING BACK.
GARDNER, AND HE RUNS IT DOWN FOR
THE FINAL OUT.
NO RUNS, NO HITS, NO ERRORS.
ONE MAN LEFT ON BASE.
FIVE IN THE BOOKS.
REDS 5, YANKEES 3.
simpler for you.g thins
Like, imagine having your
vehicle serviced...
From the comfort
of your own home.
Introducing
complimentary Lincoln Pickup
and Delivery Servicing.
Because the most important
luxury of all...
Is time.
Pickup and Delivery servicing
on the entire family
of Lincoln luxury vehicles
including a complimentary
Lincoln loaner.
This piece is so you.
I saw it and I was just like
"Oh, I have to have it..."
State Farm knows that
every one those moments,
there's one of these...
This piece is so you.
I saw it and I was just like
"I have to have it..."
From renters insurance...
...to rewards credit cards,
State Farm is here to
help life go right.
Z2BJEZ ZVPZ
Y2BJEY YVPY
THIS IS NOT ANOTHER
18-BLADE RAZOR
BECAUSE THIS IS ONEBLADE,
FROM PHILIPS NORELCO.
A BLADE FOR BEARDS AND STUBBLE.
SHAPE AND SHAVE ANY LENGTH.
AND BE YOUR BEST YOU
WITH ONEBLADE,
FROM PHILIPS NORELCO.
INNOVATION AND YOU.
PHILIPS NORELCO.
VIAGRA Single Packs,
so guys with ED can take
VIAGRA when they need it.
Ask your doctor if your heart
is healthy enough for sex.
Do not take VIAGRA if you
take nitrates for chest pain
or Adempas® for
pulmonary hypertension.
Your blood pressure could
drop to an unsafe level.
To avoid long-term injury,
seek immediate medical help
for an erection lasting
more than four hours.
Stop taking VIAGRA and
call your doctor right away
if you experience
a sudden decrease
or loss in vision or hearing.
Ask your doctor about
VIAGRA Single Packs.
>> Michael: PLAY BALL IS MLB'S
EDITION TO INSPIRE ALL FORMS OF
BASEBALL AND SOFTBALL.
TO LEARN MORE GO TO
PLAYBALL.ORG.
TIM ADLEMAN IS DONE.
NOW THEY TURN TO MICHAEL
LORENZEN.
FIVE INNINGS, THREE RUNS, TWO
WALKS AND SIX STRIKEOUTS.
14TH GAME FOR LORENZEN.
4.15 E.R.A.
HITTING .215 AGAINST HIM.
LORENZEN IS A GROUND BALL
PITCHER.
WILL FACE THREE, FOUR, FIVE IN
THE YANKEE ORDER.
AND A STRIKE FOR CASTRO WHO
DOUBLED OVER THE HEAD OF DUVALL
IN LEFT FIELD IN THE FOURTH
INNING.
LATER CAME AROUND AND SCORED.
CHOP TO FIRST.
VOTTO TAKES IT HIMSELF.
ONE AWAY.
LORENZEN HAS A 62% GROUND BALL
RATE.
THAT'S EIGHTH HIGHEST OF ALL
PITCHER WITH 50 MORE INNINGS
PITCHED.
WHEN YOU HAVE A GROUND BALL
PITCHER, DO YOU TRY TO LIFT IT
OR HIT THE BALL HARD?
>> Paul: YOU TRY TO HIT THE BALL
HARD.
YOU LOOK AT HIS ARM ANGLE.
YOU'VE GOT A LOT OF MOVEMENT
INTO RIGHTIES.
GOOD SINKER TO LEFTIES.
THE MOVEMENT OF THE BALL, YOU
THINK YOU'RE ON IT AND YOU TAKE
THE TOP HALF AND BEAT IT IN THE
GROUND.
>> Michael: PITCH TO ELLSBURY
UPSTAIRS.
REDS LEAD THE YANKEES 5-3.
>> Paul: NOT YOUR AVERAGE
SINKER.
THAT WAS 97 RIGHT THERE.
THAT KIND OF TOOK OFF.
WOW.
>> Michael: BRYAN PRICE SAID
THIS IS THE FORMULA WHY THEY ARE
17-15.
GET A DECENT OUTING OUT OF THE
STARTERS AND HOPEFULLY TURNOVER
TO THE BULLPEN THAT HE FEELS
OVERLY COMFORTABLE WITH.
HE SAID THERE'S A LOT OF OVER
CHANGEABLE PARTS IN THAT
BULLPEN.
GROUND BALL TO SHORT.
TWO OUTS.
PRICE MADE THE POINT OF SAYING
THERE AREN'T GUYS IN THE BULLPEN
THAT ARE JUST LOUNGING AROUND
EXPECTING TO BE CALLED ON.
HE SAID A GUY CAN BE IN THE
EIGHTH OR THE FOURTH AND THEY
ALL BETTER START STRETCHING IN
THE SECOND.
>> Paul: YOU GOT A LOT ON THE OF
BRYAN PRICE.
YOU MUST HAVE HAD A LONG
MEETING.
>> Michael: VERY LONG.
HERE'S AARON JUDGE.
COUPLE OF HOURS.
>> Paul: WOW.
>> Michael: PITCH INSIDE.
>> Paul: PROBABLY COOK YOU LUNCH
DOWN THERE.
YOU PROBABLY HAD IT ALL GOING.
>> Michael: 2-0 ON JUDGE.
HE'S 0 FOR 2.
STRIKEOUT AND HIT INTO A DOUBLE
PLAY.
WE'RE IN THE SIXTH.
5-3 CINCINNATI.
SO 3-0.
LET'S SEE IF GIRARDI WILL TURN
JUDGE LOOSE ON 3-0.
ON DECK IS GREGORIUS.
>> Paul: WHAT YOU LIKE ABOUT
LORENZEN, HE'S OUT THERE.
HE HITS THE SIGN AND IT'S ON HIS
WAY.
THERE'S NOT MUCH THOUGHT PROCESS
BEHIND IT.
THIS IS WHAT I'VE GOT.
THIS IS WHO I AM AS A PITCHER.
AND THERE'S NOT A LOT OF
STALLING GOING ON.
>> Michael: HERE'S GREGORIUS.
A LONG HOME RUN IN THE SECOND.
A BROKEN BAT.
HURT HIS SHOULDER IN THE WBC.
STARTED THE SEASON ON THE DL.
DID WELL SINCE COMING OFF THE
DL.
MISSED FIVE IN A ROW.
1-0.
1-1.
NOW, YOU LOOK UP AT A DEFICIT
FOR THE YANKEES AND THAT REALLY
DOES NOT UNNERVE THIS TEAM.
THIS TEAM FEELS VERY COMFORTABLE
GOING INTO LATE INNINGS, DOWN.
OTHER NOT, BUT IF THEY DO, THEY
FEEL LIKE THEY CAN COME BACK.
THEY KNOW THEY'VE COME BACK.
THEY WERE TRAILING THE ORIOLES
9-1 THAT THEY ENDED UP WINNING.
2-1.
I GUESS, PAUL, THE MORE YOU DO
IT, THE MORE YOU BELIEVE YOU DO
IT AGAIN.
>> Paul: ABSOLUTELY.
YOU WANT TO GET IN SITUATIONS
WHERE YOU'RE ACCUSTOMED TO
WINNING.
THIS IS THEIR FORMULA.
>> Michael: LINED INTO CENTER
FIELD.
IT IS A BASE HIT.
GREGORIUS IS 3 FOR 3.
JUDGE WILL STOP AT SECOND.
>> Paul: YOU CAN SEE THE YANKEE
OFFENSE LAST YEAR.
WE TALKED ABOUT IT, MICHAEL.
WE DID A LOT OF GAMES WHERE YOU
COULD TRY TO FIGURE OUT HOW THIS
TEAM COULD SCORE RUNS AND THIS
YEAR IT'S ALMOST TOTALLY
BACKWARD.
IT'S LIKE HOW CAN THEY NOT SCORE
RUNS.
EVERYBODY, ONE THROUGH NINE, ARE
ABLE TO SWING THE BAT.
>> Michael: HERE'S CHRIS CARTER.
HE'S GLAD ADLEMAN IS OUT OF THE
GAME.
FIRST AND SECOND.
TWO MEN OUT HERE IN THE SIXTH.
THERE'S A STRIKE.
96 MILES AN HOUR.
>> Paul: YOU LOOK AT -- PROBABLY
A BETTER MATCH-UP FOR CARTER.
ADLEMAN REALLY MET WITH HIM WITH
THE CHANGE-UP, WITH THE
CURVEBALL, GETTING AHEAD IN THE
COUNT.
>> Michael: 0-2.
>> Paul: THIS IS WHERE CARTER
HAS TROUBLE.
THIS IS WHERE THEY START TO, YOU
KNOW, THROW STUFF OUTSIDE THE
STRIKE ZONE.
HE'S VERY ACCEPTABLE TO THAT
STRIKEOUT.
>> Michael: JUDGE OFF SECOND.
GREGORIUS OFF FIRST.
AND THE 0-2.
OFF THE GLOVE OF MESORACO AND
THE RUNNERS WILL MOVE UP.
SCORED A WILD PITCH.
NOW WITH THE SPEED AT SECOND,
YOU DON'T HAVE TO HIT THE BALL
OVER THE WALL.
A SINGLE TIES THE GAME.
>> Paul: THIS BALL JUST TAKES
OFF.
YOU LOSE THAT BALL WITH THAT
MASK BECAUSE YOU DON'T SEE WELL
ABOVE.
THE CATCHER'S MIT NOT VERY
FORGIVING WHEN YOU DON'T HIT THE
MIDDLE OF IT.
>> Michael: 1-2.
2-2.
>> Paul: BOY, JUST UP AND IN.
HAVING A HARD TIME CONTROLLING
IT AGAINST CARTER.
>> Michael: AND THAT HITS
CARTER.
AND THAT WILL LOAD THE BASES.
YANKEES ARE USED TO THIS.
LAST NIGHT THREE BATTERS GOT HIT
IN ONE INNING.
AND JOE GIRARDI SAID I KNOW IT
WASN'T ON PURPOSE.
HE SAID, BUT YOU DO HAVE TO BE
CAREFUL.
YESTERDAY WAS DREW STOREN.
>> Paul: AND THERE WERE THREE
PITCHES.
RIGHT OUT OF HIS HAND.
I TALKED TO CHASE HEADLEY TODAY
AND HE SAID THERE WAS NO WAY OUT
OF IT.
HE JUST OVERTHREW SOME PITCHES.
>> Michael: PITCHING COACH MATT
JENKINS COMES OUT AND TALKS WITH
LORENZEN.
THAT WILL BRING UP TORREYES WITH
THE BASES LOADED.
SABATHIA DUE UP AFTER THAT BUT
THE YANKEES HAVE MATT HOLLIDAY
ON DECK TO PINCH-HIT FOR
SABATHIA.
TORREYES A NOTORIOUS FIRST BALL
HITTER.
>> Paul: NOBODY ON AND THE NEXT
THING YOU KNOW YOU'RE A BASE HIT
FROM TYING THIS GAME UP.
>> Michael: SWINGS AT THE FIRST
PITCH AND GROUNDS IT BACK.
TORREYES IS THE YANKEES SUPER
UTILITY GUY.
CAN PLAY SECOND, SHORT, THIRD.
TODAY HE'S AT THIRD.
HE CAN ALSO PLAY THE OUTFIELD IN
A PITCH AND HE'S THEIR EMERGENCY
CATCHER BEHIND GARRY SANCHEZ AND
AUSTIN ROMINE.
>> Paul: HE'S A FREE SWINGER
OBVIOUSLY.
HE'S HAD A WALK AND HIT BY A
PITCH.
HE CAME OUT OF THE ON DECK
CIRCLE SWINGING AT THAT FIRST
PITCH.
>> Michael: CHOP TO SHORT.
GOES TO SECOND.
THEY GET THE FORCE AND THAT WILL
DO IT.
NO RUNS.
NO ERRORS.
AND THE BASES ARE LEFT LOADED.
WE GO TO THE BOTTOM OF THE SIXTH
INNING.
5-3 CINCINNATI.
Well, if a lot od
off a bridge, would you?
You hungry?
I'm okay right --
I'm...
I'm becoming my,
uh, mother.
It's been hard,
but some of the stuff he says
is actually pretty helpful.
Pumpkin, bundling our home and
auto insurance is a good deal!
Like buying in bulk!
That's fun, right?
Progressive can't protect you
from becoming your parents,
but we can protect
your home and auto.
Progressive can't protect you
from becoming your parents,
♪  ♪
Ugh, no bars.
Oh no, looks like somebody
needs a new network.
When I got this unlimited plan
they told me they were
all the same.
They're not.
Verizon has the largest,
most-reliable
4G LTE
network in America.
It's basically made for
places like this.
Honey, what if it
was just us out here?
Right.
So, I ordered
you a car.
Thank you.
You don't want to be
out here at night
'cause of
the, uh, coyotes.
Ok, thanks, bud.
Bye.
Be nice to have your car
for some shelter.
Bye.
When it really, really matters,
you need the best network
and the best unlimited.
Just $45 per line
for four lines.
>> Michael: YOU GREW UP WITH
THAT TEAM, PAUL O'NEAL.
THE BIG RED MACHINE.
>> Paul: A LOT OF HISTORY IN
THIS TEAM.
FIRST PROFESSIONAL TEAM.
1869.
WOW.
>> Michael: START IN THE BOTTOM
OF THE SIXTH.
1-0.
REDS LEAD 5-3.
YANKEES HAD AN OPPORTUNITY IN
THE TOP OF THE SIXTH INNING.
COMING INTO TODAY, SABATHIA
FIRST OR SECOND, BIG NUMBERS AS
ACTIVE PITCHER.
THAT ONE POPPED UP.
THAT MAKES THE ROOF OF THE
DUGOUT.
>> Paul: THAT'S WHEN YOU WOULD
RUN OUT AND GET THE BOX SCORES
OUT OF THE NEWSPAPER.
NOW IT'S IMMEDIATE.
I KIND OF MISS THOSE BOX SCORES.
GREW UP UP THAT WAY.
>> Michael: ABSOLUTELY.
GROUNDED TO SHORT.
GREGORIUS.
AND THERE'S ONE AWAY.
BIG RED MACHINE.
CHAMPIONSHIP IN '75 AND '76
AGAINST THE YANKEES.
TAKE IT OVER, PAUL.
YOU KNEW THESE GUYS.
>> Paul: JOE MORGAN.
SAW HIM AT THE BALLPARK.
GEORGE FOSTER.
JOHNNY BENCH.
HE WAS BEST THE POSITION PLAYER
AT WHAT HE DID THAT EVER PLAYED
THE GAME.
PETE ROSE HERE LAST NIGHT.
>> Michael: IN '75 THEY WON 108
GAMES AND THEY BEAT THE RED SOX
IN SEVEN.
HAD UNBELIEVABLE SERIES.
LORENZEN IS NOT YOUR BASE HIT
PITCHER AS A HITTER.
ON APRIL 6th THIS YEAR, GAME
WINNING PINCH-HIT HOME RUN
AGAINST THE PHILLIES.
FIRST PINCH-HIT HOME RUN IN
MAJOR LEAGUE BASEBALL SINCE
MICHAEL OWENS IN 2009 ALSO WITH
THE REDS.
HE HAD TWO CAREER HOME RUNS.
HIS FIRST ONE WAS AN EMOTIONAL
ONE FOR HIM.
FIRST TEAM BACK SINCE HIS FATHER
HAD DIED.
THAT WAS ON AUGUST 19th OF LAST
YEAR.
SABATHIA HAS TO BE CAREFUL WITH
LORENZEN.
>> Paul: PRETTY GOOD SWING.
THAT'S ONE OF THE KIDS THAT GREW
UP BEING A BASEBALL PLAYER.
PROBABLY PLAYED ALL THE
POSITIONS OF SHORTSTOP, PITCHER.
GOOD HITTER.
>> Michael: YOU KNOW HE'S A
PRETTY GOOD HITTER BECAUSE HE
WENT DOWN TO ONE KNEE.
A LOT OF PITCHERS DON'T DO THAT.
CHOP TO THIRD.
TORREYES WAITS BACK FOR THE HOP.
NICE SCOOP.
LORENZEN BEAT IT OUT.
HE'S AN ATHLETE.
>> Paul: HAD TO WAIT BACK.
BALL DOWN IN THE DIRT A LITTLE
BIT.
SAFE AT FIRST.
>> Michael: OR IS HE?
THEY'RE GOING TO CHALLENGE.
THE ONLY QUESTION, DID THE BALL
ROLL IN THE GLOVE AND IT DOESN'T
SEEM AS IF IT DID.
>> Paul: CARTER MADE A GOOD
PLAY.
THAT WASN'T A SHORT HOP.
HE'S OUT.
>> Michael: THE YANKEES WILL
CHALLENGE.
SEE IF THIS IS OVERTURNED.
FIRST BASE UMPIRE.
THE BALL HITS THE GLOVE BEFORE
THE FOOT CAME DOWN.
HE WILL GO OVER WITH THE CREW
CHIEF WHO'S AT SECOND.
AND THEY WILL LOOK AT IT BACK IN
THE STUDIOS IN NEW YORK CITY AND
THE AREA OF MANHATTAN CALLED
CHELSEA.
>> Paul: GOOD OLD CHELSEA.
TRIBECA, THEY'RE DOING ALL KIND
OF STUFF THERE.
>> Michael: DOES WONDER HOW YOU
LOOK AT THE REPLAY AND GET IT IN
HALF A SECOND AND WHY IT'S
TAKING THIS LONG.
>> Paul: THEY DON'T TRUST US UP
HERE ANYMORE, MIKE.
>> Michael: LET'S SEE.
THEY HAVE OVERTURNED IT.
HE'S OUT.
AND THAT PLAY WAS ALL CARTER.
>> Paul: YES.
YOU WATCH CARTER'S EYES, EVERY
ONCE IN A WHILE YOU'RE FORTUNATE
AS A PLAYER.
THAT BALL WAS NOT A SHORT HOP IN
THE DIRT.
IT WENT OFF THE GRASS.
WATCH HIS EYES KIND OF COME UP.
THAT BALL JUST FINDS THE GLOVE.
>> Michael: BILLY HAMILTON.
0-1.
BIG SHORT AND PAST TORREYES AND
INTO LEFT FIELD.
AND GOING FOR TWO.
THE THROW IS IN TIME.
HE GOT HIM.
HE GETS THE SPEEDY HAMILTON
TRYING TO GET A DOUBLE.
GORDON WHO GOT TO THE BALL
QUICKLY AND FIRED A STRIKE.
THE TAG APPLIED BY CASTRO.
What are you doing? It's 11pm.
I can explain...
You should be out there
disappointing your father.
I need to clean this place up.
Bloopy, bad
judgement and loopy.
Hunger keeps inventing
new problems,
so we invented
SNICKERS® Crisper.
On September 9, 2010,
PG&E learned a tragic lesson we
can never forget.
This gas pipeline ruptured in
San Bruno.
The explosion and fire killed
eight people.
PG&E was convicted of six felony
charges including
five violations of the U.S.
Pipeline Safety Act and
obstructing an NTSB
investigation.
PG&E was fined, placed under an
outside monitor,
given five years of probation,
and required to perform 10,000
hours of community service.
We are deeply sorry.
We failed our customers in
San Bruno.
While an apology alone will
never be enough,
actions can make PG&E safer.
And that's why we've replaced
hundreds of miles of gas
pipeline,
adopted new leak detection
technology
that is one-thousand times more
sensitive,
and built a state-of-the-art gas
operations center.
We can never forget what
happened in San Bruno.
That's why we're working every
day to make PG&E
the safest energy company in the
nation.
>> Michael: TIME FOR GRIP THE
MOMENT.
>> Paul: GREAT PLAY BY BRETT
GARDNER.
IF YOU WATCH WHAT HAPPENED,
BILLY HAMILTON PROBABLY IS SAFE
IF HE KEEPS HIS HAPPENEDS
STRAIGHT OUT.
HE KIND OF PULLS THEM BACK.
WATCH HIS HANDS GO BACK.
GIVES CASTRO AN OPPORTUNITY TO
TAG HIM BEFORE HE GETS TO THE
BASE.
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENS WHEN YOU'RE
GOING THAT FAST.
THE FLAPS GET DOWN.
YOU CAN'T KEEP THEM EXTENDED.
>> Michael: C.C. LIKED THE PLAY.
YOU HAVE TO BE IMPRESSED WHEN
BILLY HAMILTON IS THROWN OUT AT
ANY BASE.
WILL PINCH-HIT FOR C.C.
SABATHIA.
TAKES THE STRIKE HICKS IS ONE
HIT SHY OF QUALIFYING.
.462 ON-BASE PERCENTAGE.
HIS LAST FOUR GAMES HIT .476
SCORING SEVEN RUNS.
CHOP TO FIRST.
VOTTO WILL GET IT.
ONE AWAY.
YANKEE OUTFIELD HAS DONE SOME
JOB OVER THE FIRST 30 GAMES.
YANKEES OUTFIELDERS -- THE
SECOND PLACE TEAM, THE
NATIONALS, 3.0: YANKEES ALMOST
DOUBLE THE SECOND PLACE TEAM.
>> Michael: LOT OF REDUCTION IN
THE OUTFIELD.
FUN PROBLEM TO HAVE AS YOU GET
FOUR GUYS THAT ARE DOING
EVERYTHING FOR YOU.
YOU REALLY CAN'T DH ONE OF THEM.
YOU'VE GOT TO FIGURE BRETT
GARDNER, ELLSBURY, EVERY TIME A
LEFTY PITCHERS, ONE OF THEM IS
GOING TO BE OUT.
>> Michael: LOW TO GARDNER.
2-0.
THE YANKEES WANT TO EXTEND THEIR
INNING STREAK, THEY HAVE NINE
COME FROM BEHIND WIN THIS IS
YEAR.
THEIR RECORD OF 21-9.
THE BEST RECORD THEY'VE HAD AT
THE 30 GAME SINCE 2003 AND THAT
WAS THE YEAR THEY WENT TO THE
WORLD SERIES.
>> Paul: TALK ABOUT THAT
OUTFIELD JAM.
GARDNER LAST NINE GAMES IN THE
GAME HIT .375 WITH SIX HOME
RUNS.
FIRST 18 GAMES NO HOME RUNS.
HE'S BEEN HOT.
>> Michael: AND GARDNER WORKS A
WALK.
SO WITH GARDNER AT FIRST, THAT
BRINGS UP SANCHEZ AS THE TYING
RUN IN A 5-3 REDS LEAD.
SANCHEZ WITH A LONG HOME RUN IN
THE FIRST INNING.
THEN GROUND TO THIRD AND STRUCK
OUT.
SECOND IN THE ROOKIE OF THE YEAR
LAST YEAR.
THAT'S HOW INCREDIBLE THE
TWO-MONTHS WERE AT THE END OF
THE SEASON.
WHAT HAPPENED IN THOSE TWO
MONTHS FOR THE YANKEES, THEY
TRADED A TRAY BELTRAN, CHAPMAN,
MILLER.
THEY RESTOCKED THEIR FARM SYSTEM
WHERE IS'S NOW RATED EITHER THE
BEST OR SECOND BEST IN ALL OF
BASEBALL.
GARY SANCHEZ GETTING A CHANCE TO
SHOW WHAT HE'S ALL ABOUT.
THE REDS FIVE RUNS IN THE SECOND
INNING.
SEND TEN BATTERS TO THE PLATE.
YANKEES WITH A RUN IN THE FIRST,
A RUN IN THE SECOND, A RUN IN
THE FOURTH.
>> Paul: BRETT GARDNER IN HIS
CAREER STEALS, HE DOESN'T RUN AS
MUCH AS HE DID IN HIS EARLY
DAYS.
YOU'VE GOT SANCHEZ.
A LOT OF TIMES AS A BASE STEALER
YOU'VE GOT TO BE PATIENT.
YOU'VE GOT TO GIVE THESE GUYS A
CHANCE TO SWING THE BAT.
TIE THIS THING UP WITH ONE
SWING.
A LOT OF TIMES THOSE GROUND
BALLS ARE JUST BECAUSE IT'S
FEEDING THE BAT.
I GUYS AREN'T GETTING OUT
EXTENDED.
IT'S KIND OF OVERPOWERING.
>> Michael: 1-2.
BLOCKED BY MESORACO.
>> Paul: HAVEN'T SEEN A LOT OF
BREAKING BALLS.
GOOD JOB GUY MESORACO TO KEEP
THAT BALL IN FRONT OF HIM.
AND THE PITCH.
GROUNDED FOUL.
>> Paul: GOOD PITCH THERE.
THAT BALL THERE HAD A LITTLE
MOVEMENT.
IT WAS ALL HORIZONTAL.
A PITCH THAT A HITTER LOVES.
GOOD SWING.
BALL KIND OF TAILING INTO HIM,
BUT A GREAT PITCH TO HIT.
>> Michael: REALLY NICE PLAY.
>> Paul: BARE HAND LIKE IT WAS
NOTHING.
HE WAS A BUCKEYE FAN.
DID YOU SEE THAT?
>> Michael: PAUL, I GOT GOOD
NEWS.
THE MOON IS BACK.
>> Paul: YOU BETTER HURRY UP AND
TAKE A PICTURE.
>> Michael: ONE DAY AWAY FROM A
FOOL MOON.
GARDNER LEADS OFF FIRST.
HE DOESN'T KNOW WHERE IT IS.
GARDNER MOVES TO SECOND ON THE
WILD PITCH.
>> Paul: ANOTHER BREAKING BALL.
HE'S NOT BEEN ABLE TO LOCATE
THIS.
THE GLOVE CAUGHT THE WRONG WAY.
HARD TO KEEP IT IN FRONT OF YOU.
KIND OF A BACKHAND THERE.
KIND OF RICOCHETS AWAY.
REPLAY LOOKS LIKE HE HAS SO MUCH
TIME.
THAT IS SO QUICK.
IT HAS TO HAPPEN.
>> Michael: 3-2.
SWING AND A MISS.
THAT GETS AWAY FROM MESORACO.
AND THERE'S TWO OUTS.
>> Paul: THAT 3-2 BREAKING BALL
AND AGAIN BOUNCES.
GARY SANCHEZ, LIKE A DEAD
FASTBALL.
BRETT GARDNER GETS A GOOD READ.
NOTHING HE CAN DO.
>> Michael: AND ANOTHER TRIP TO
THE MOUND.
THEY HAVE A TOUGH HITTER COMING
UP.
STARLIN CASTRO.
CASTRO 1 FOR 3.
HITTING .357.
TWO HARD THROWERS IN THE
BULLPEN.
PERALTA IS THE ONLY LEFTY IN THE
THEY HAVE ELLSBURY UP NEXT.
AFTER CASTRO.
SO CASTRO ONE FOR THREE.
DOUBLE OVER THE HEAD OF DUVALL.
BROKEN BAT SINGLE.
HAMILTON IS VERY SHALLOW CENTER
FIELD.
CASTRO HAS POWER.
SIX HOME RUNS.
TIME IS CALLED.
WOULDN'T YOU SAY THAT'S TOO
SHALLOW?
>> Paul: THAT'S ALMOST DARING
SOMEBODY.
ALMOST DARING SOMEBODY, SHOWING
HOW FAST YOU ARE TO HIT A BALL
OVER YOUR HEAD.
TWO-RUN GAME.
YOU'RE LATE IN THE GAME.
YOU'RE PLAYING NOTHING OVER YOUR
HEAD.
NO DOUBLES.
BILLY HAMILTON KNOWS THIS
BALLPARK AND HE KNOWS HIS SPEED.
>> Michael: FLY BALL, RIGHT
FIELD.
GOING BACK.
STILL BACK.
HE'LL MAKE THE PLAY RIGHT IN
FRONT OF THE WARNING TRACK FOR
THE FINAL OUT OF THE SEVENTH.
NO RUNS, NO HITS, NO ERRORS.
TIME FOR THE STRETCH IN
CINCINNATI.
5-3 REDS.
A naturally aspirated
5.0-liter V8 engine.
A 10-speed Direct-Shift
transmission.
A meticulously
crafted interior.
All of these are feats
of engineering.
Combining them with
near-perfect weight
distribution...
...is a feat of amazing.
Experience the first-ever
471-horsepower
Lexus LC 500
or the Multistage
Hybrid LC 500h.
Experience Amazing.
It's great to finally meet you.
Your parents have been
talking about you for years.
They're all about
me saving for a house,
or starting a
college fund for my son.
Actually, I want to know
what you're thinking.
Knowing that the most
important goals are yours.
It's how Edward Jones
makes sense of investing.
Cricket has something
epic for you.
Our plans start at
only $30 a month.
We've got more 4G LTE coverage
than T-Mobile or Sprint.
Plus switch now, and get
a brand new smartphone for free.
Cricket Wireless.
Something to smile about.
This is how it feels
when you eat a Subway®
$6 Footlong Sub of the Day.
It's the taste you love,
at a price you can't
get enough of.
The $6 Footlong Sub of the Day.
Seven days, seven Footlongs,
seven more ways to enjoy
Subway®.
>>> THE REDS HAVE WON FIVE
CHAMPIONSHIPS IN THEIR HISTORY.
1919, 1940, 1975, 1976, AND
1990.
OUTSIDE TO COZART.
SMILING.
THEIR TEAM'S UP 5-3.
BETANCES WITH AN ARSENAL OF
CURVEBALLS.
SEE WHICH ONE IS MORE DEADLY.
>> Paul: THE NIGHT THAT HE'LL
COME IN AND THROW 10, 12 PITCHES
AND THREE STRIKEOUTS IS THE NICE
THAT HE HAD THIS GREAT
CURVEBALL.
TOO HARD TO PICK UP FROM A GUY
HIS SIZE.
YOU HAVE TO LOOK FASTBALL WHEN
THE GUY'S THROWING 100.
>> Michael: COZART WALKS.
WE WILL GO TO CHRIS MYERS.
>> THANKS, MICHAEL.
NATIONALS IN BALTIMORE.
TIE GAME.
JIMENEZ PITCHING.
ADAM LIND WITH A THREE-RUN
HOMER.
MLP "WHIPAROUND" WITH ALL THE
HIGHLIGHTS IMMEDIATELY AFTER THE
GAME.
>> Michael: THANK YOU, CHRIS.
BOTTOM OF THE SEVENTH INNING.
5-3.
REDS OVER THE YANKS.
PITCH INSIDE.
TO JOEY VOTTO.
PITCH STAYS IN THE GAME IN LEFT
FIELD.
BETANCES WILL BAT IN THE LEADOFF
SPOT VACATED BY BRETT GARDNER.
NOW WE TOLD YOU THE REDS WILL
RUN AND YOU CAN RUN ON HIM.
>> Paul: YEAH.
ANYTIME YOU GET A POWER PITCHER
YOU CAN RUN SLOW ANYTIME YOU GET
A JUMP.
A LOT OF TIMES YOU STEAL ON THE
PITCHER, NOT THE CATCHER.
GOOD MATCH-UP, THE NATIONALS AND
BALTIMORE.
AS GOOD AS THE YANKEES HAVE
BEEN, THEY COME IN HALF A GAME
UP FROM BALTIMORE.
OFF TO A GREAT STORE.
>> Michael: SIX PITCHES FROM
BETANCES ALL OUT OF THE STRIKE
ZONE.
ORIOLES JUST GOT BAD NEWS AGAIN
TODAY.
BRITAIN IS GOING TO BE OUT AT
LEAST TWO MORE MONTHS.
3-0.
SEVEN IN A ROW OUT OF THE ZONE.
PITCHED IN THAT 18-INNING GAME
AT WRIGLEY FIELD.
HE HAD YESTERDAY OFF.
>> Paul: THIS IS SUPPOSED TO BE
THE EASY INNING WHEN YOU GET THE
CHAPMAN AND BETANCES.
>> Michael: EIGHT IN A ROW.
SO COZART WALKS.
FIRST AND SECOND, NOBODY OUT.
AND A TRIP TO THE MOUND.
>> Paul: LARRY SPENT SOME TIME
HERE, THE PITCHING COACH, WITH
THE REDS.
>> Michael: WE MENTION THE REDS
ARE A TEAM IN TRAN SIG.
THAT'S WHY THEIR GOOD STARTERS
HAVE BEEN SURPRISING.
THEY WON 68 GAMES LAST YEAR.
AND THEY'VE GOT RID OF THEIR BIG
PLAYS.
JAY BRUCE.
CHAPMAN, CUETO.
FRAZIER.
MIKE LEE, BRANDON PHILLIPS.
SOME PEOPLE EXPECT COZART IN THE
LAST YEAR OF HIS CONTRACT THAT
HE WILL BE TRADED AT SOME POINT
THIS YEAR AS WELL.
>> Michael: MESORACO POSSIBLY.
THERE'S A COUPLE GUYS STILL OUT
THERE THAT --
>> Michael: AND BRYAN PRICE SAID
2015 AND '16, BEYOND PAINFUL.
>> Paul: OH, YEAH.
>> Michael: SO THE CONFERENCE IS
OVER.
AND HERE'S DUVALL.
SWING AND A MISS.
THAT WAS A BALL AS WELL.
0-1.
>> Paul: HERE'S DELLIN'S
BREAKING BALL.
JUST OFF THE OUTSIDE CORNER.
EVERY TIME YOU SEE SOMETHING
WHERE THE GAME HAS CHANGED A
LITTLE BIT, IT'S, LIKE, WOW, A
COUPLE WALKS.
YOU GET A SWING.
FIRST PITCH.
>> Michael: WOULDN'T THE OTHER
SCHOOL OF THOUGHT BE HE HAS TO
CALL A STRIKE.
>> Paul: BETANCES, YOU DON'T
WANT TO GET TO THIS POINT.
IF A GUY IS GOING TO DIG A HOLE,
YOU'VE GOT TO LET HIM DIG IT.
HEAVY POWER OUT THERE IN THE
MIDDLE.
HE HAD A LONG CAREER BACK WITH
THE REDS.
CASTELLINI YESTERDAY, BOY THEY
WERE GLAD TO HAVE HIM BACK IN
THE ORGANIZATION.
>> Michael: THE OWNERS OF THE
REDS.
AND THE 0-2.
JUST UPSTAIRS.
1-2.
REDS 5, YANKEES 3.
WE'RE IN THE BOTTOM OF THE
SEVENTH INNING.
REDS HAVE RUNNERS ON FIRST AND
SECOND.
NOBODY OUT.
DELLIN BETANCES HAS COME ON AND
RELIEVED C.C. SABATHIA.
1-2.
SWING AND A MISS.
GOT HIM.
100 MILES AP HOUR.
GOT IT BY DUVALL.
ONE AWAY.
>> Paul: YOU SEE A COUPLE
BREAKING BALLS EARLY IN THE
COUNT.
IT'S IN THE BACK OF YOUR MIND.
100 MILAN HOUR FASTBALLS IN
SANCHEZ'S GLOVE.
THIS IS THE PROBLEM WITH BITAN
-- BETANCES.
HE CAN GET HIMSELF IN TROUBLE
THEN GET RIGHT OUT OF IT.
>> Michael: SUAREZ.
BREAKING BALL AS SUAREZ WAS
MOVING BACK AND WHISPERS ACROSS
THE INSIDE CORNER.
>> Paul: YOU'LL SEE THAT
REACTION FROM A RIGHTY.
THAT BALL OUT OF HIS HAND LOOKS
LIKE IT'S RIGHT AT YOU.
IN YOUR MIND IS NOT GOING TO
CLICK IN AND SAY I'M GOING TO
WAIT AND SEE WHERE IT IS.
YOU JUST BAIL.
>> Michael: SANCHEZ WANTS TO
TALK WITH BETANCES.
YANKEES OBVIOUSLY WANT TO KEEP
IT RIGHT HERE.
THEY HAVE A TWO-RUN HOLE TO DIG
OUT OF.
SUAREZ AT THE PLATE.
SCHEBLER IN THE ON-DECK CIRCLE.
FOUL BACK TO THE SCREEN.
0-2.
>> Paul: THE BEST PITCH YOU'RE
GOING TO GET FROM BETANCES RIGHT
THERE.
LITTLE HANGING BREAKING BALL.
GOOD SWING.
NOT A LOT OF BITE ON THIS ONE.
UP IN THE STRIKE ZONE.
SUAREZ STILL A HIT TORE HANG ONE
BUT JUST MISSED THAT ONE.
>> Michael: THE 0-2.
SWUNG AND MISSED.
TWO AWAY.
>> Paul: THERE'S A DIFFERENCE OF
A GOOD CURVEBALL AND A BAD
CURVEBALL.
THE ONE BEFORE YOU SAW FOULED
BACK AND THEN HE THREW HIS BAT.
COMPLETELY DIFFERENT SWING.
WATCH THE BREAK ON THIS.
THIS IS A COMPLETELY DIFFERENT
PITCH.
DIFFERENT SWING.
>> Michael: NOW TO BRING UP
SCHEBLER.
SINGLED AND SCORED.
WAS HIT BY A PITCH AND STOLE A
BASE.
BREAKING BALL, STRIKE.
0-1.
>> Paul: WHEN HE GETS IN
TROUBLE, I THINK HE TRUSTS THAT
BREAKING BALL MORE THAN HE DOES
HIS FASTBALL.
HE'LL USE THE FASTBALL LATE IN
THE COUNT TO TRY TO GET THE
STRIKEOUT BEFORE HE REALLY DROPS
THAT CURVEBALL.
THERE'S A GOOD 100 MILE AN HOUR.
NOW HE'S ON THE BRINK OF
STRIKING OUT THREE IN A ROW.
>> Michael: NINE OUT OF TEN
PITCHES HAVE BEEN STRIKES AFTER
WALKING THE FIRST TWO.
STRIKE THREE.
HE STRIKES OUT THREE IN A ROW TO
GET OUT OF A PROBLEM.
NO RUNS.
NO HITS.
NO ERRORS.
WE GO TO THE EIGHTH.
5-3 REDS.
The show's about to start!
How do I look?
Like a bald penguin.
[ laughing ]
Show me the
Billboard Music Awards.
Show me Top Artist.
Show me the
Top Hot 100 Artist.
They give awards for being
hot and 100 years old?
We'll take 2!
[ laughing ]
XFINITY X1 gives you
exclusive access to the best
of the Billboard Music Awards
just by using your voice.
The Billboard Music Awards.
Sunday, May 21st eight
seven central only on ABC.
>> Michael: MLB ON FS1.
SPONSORED BY -- AFTER WALKING
THE 50 TWO BATTERS, YANKEES ARE
DOWN 5-3 AS WE START THE EIGHTH
INNING.
>> Paul: MICHAEL, WHEN YOU LOOK
BACK AT THAT INNING AND WHEN IT
STARTED, YOU'VE GOT EIGHT
STRAIGHT BALLS.
BALL FOUR.
THEN YOU'VE GOT A SWING AND A
MISS ON A PITCH OFF THE PLATE.
AND THEN BETANCES FOUND HIS
RELEASE AND YOU GET THREE
STRIKEOUTS IN A ROW.
>> Michael: NOW WE GET ANOTHER
LOOK AT A HARD THROWING
RIGHT-HANDER.
THIS KID CAN PITCH.
USUALLY CLOSES GAMES FOR THE
REDS.
THIS WILL BE THE 12th GAME.
19 STRIKEOUTS IN 16 1/3 INNINGS.
MOVES INTO RIGHT.
ELLSBURY WILL LEAD OFF AGAINST
--
>> Paul: YOU SEE THE LONG PANTS
AND THE WHITE SHOES.
ALL I CAN THINK ABOUT IS COMING
THROUGH THE REDS ORGANIZATION IN
THE MINOR LEAGUES, WE HAD TO
WEAR THE WOOL STOCKINGS, THE
STIRRUPS AND YOU HAD TO SHOW SO
MUCH OF IT OR YOU WERE FINED AND
WE ALL HAD BLACK SHOES.
THAT'S HOW FAR IT'S COME.
IT WAS COOL TO POOL THOSE
STIRRUPS UP.
YOU COULDN'T PULL THOSE UP.
>> Michael: GROUND.
BEATS ELLSBURY TO THE BAG.
LET'S SEE IF YOU ACTUALLY
FOLLOWED THE RULES, PAUL.
>> Paul: SEE THAT?
I HAD THEM UP.
>> Michael: LITTLE LOW THERE.
>> Paul: WE STARTED TO PUSH THE
LIMITS A LITTLE BIT.
>> Michael: REALLY CRUSHED THAT
ONE.
>> Paul: WOW.
THAT'S THE OLD RIVER FRONT
STADIUM.
THE HIGHLIGHTS ARE THE OLD
THAT STADIUM IS NOT EVEN AROUND
ANYMORE.
>> Michael: YOU'RE LUCKY THEY'RE
NOT BLACK AND WHITE.
>> Paul: IT LOOKS LIKE ONE OF
THE EDITED VERSIONS AND THEY
ADDED COLOR TO IT.
>> Michael: JUDGE FOUL ITS BACK.
NOW 1-1.
>> Paul: THEY'VE DONE A GOOD JOB
WITH JUDGE TONIGHT.
KEEP THE BALL AWAY AND THEN
GETTING OUTS BY JAMMING HIM IN.
>> Michael: HARD PITCHER TO
SQUARE UP.
BROKEN BAT.
BLOOPER INTO RIGHT FIELD.
IT IS A BASE HIT.
SO JUDGE PICKED UP A BROKEN BAT
SINGLE.
>> Paul: DIED A HERO, THOUGH.
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
SEE THE ARM ANGLE THERE.
HE DROPPED DOWN THROUGH SIDEARM.
BALL FOUR IN ON HIM.
IN A COLD NIGHT, IF YOU DON'T
SQUARE IT UP PRETTY GOOD, YOU DO
THIS WHEN YOU'RE THIS STRONG.
STILL SBOK KNOCK IT INTO RIGHT
FIELD FOR A HIT.
>> Michael: JUDGE HAS BEEN ON
TWICE.
SINGLE AND A WALK IN THE SIXTH
INNING.
HERE'S DIDI.
>> Paul: JOEY VOTTO OVER THERE
KIND OF PEEKING OVER HIS
SHOULDER, LIKE, WOW, DUDE IS
BIG.
>> Michael: CHECK SWING.
VOTTO IS NOT A SMALL GUY, BUT
JUDGE BIG.
JUDGE JUST TRIED TO STEAL SOME
BASES.
HOLLIDAY SAID BIG GUY, DON'T BE
STEALING BASES.
EVERY TIME YOU SLIDE, IT'S LIKE
A CAR CRASH.
WE DON'T NEED.
THAT WE NEED YOU TO HIT HOME
RUNS.
SO LAYOFF STEALING BASES.
>> Paul: YOU PLAYED BASEBALL
BECAUSE YOU DIDN'T WANT TO BE A
DEFENSIVE END.
DON'T GO SLIDING INTO SECOND
BASE.
>> Michael: HOLLIDAY AND JUDGE
HAVE FORMED A UNIQUE BOND.
HOLLIDAY SAID HE'S ONE OF THE
GREATEST ATHLETES I'VE EVER BEEN
AROUND.
1-1.
2-1.
2-2.
>> Paul: IGLESIAS IS ONE OF
THOSE THAT SLING THE BALL.
NOT COMPLETELY SIDEARM, BUT YOU
GIVE A LOT OF LIFE.
THE FINISH ON IT GET A LOT OF
MOVEMENT.
SNAPS IT.
>> Michael: SO THE COUNT 3-2 ON
GREGORIUS.
GREGORIUS IS 3 FOR 3.
COUPLE OF SINGLES AND A HOME
RUN.
TWO RUNS BATTED IN.
JUDGE LEADS OFF FIRST.
CARTER IS ON DECK.
AND THE PITCH.
HIGH FLY BALL, CENTER FIELD.
HAMILTON IS THERE FOR THE SECOND
OUT.
>> Paul: BEST PITCH HE HAD.
JUST GOT UNDER IT A LITTLE BIT.
THIS PITCH YOU SAW OVER THE
MIDDLE OF THE PLATE.
KIND OF RUN IT BACK.
RIGHT OFF THE END OF THE BAT.
JUST UNDER IT.
AMAZING AS A HITTER YOUR
REACTION.
IMMEDIATELY YOU KNOW YOU HAD A
GOOD PITCH TO HIT AND IT JUST
MISSES.
>> Michael: HERE'S CHRIS CARTER.
0 FOR 2.
COUPLE STRIKEOUTS.
WAS HIT BY A PITCH.
SO IGLESIAS IS THE THIRD
PITCHER.
ADLEMAN STARTED WITH FIVE.
LORENZEN CAME ON AND HIT TWO.
NOW IGLESIAS.
GREEN IS UP NEXT.
>> Paul: GOT TO BE LOOSE BY NOW.
>> Michael: YOU WOULD THINK.
1-1.
TEMPERATURE'S DROPPED JUST A
LITTLE BIT.
WE ARE IN THE EIGHTH INNING NOW.
THE RAIN HAS HELD OFF HERE IN
CINCINNATI.
CHOP TO THIRD.
SUAREZ FEELS.
SET AND FIRES.
GETS CARTER FOR THE FINAL OUT OF
THE EIGHTH.
NO RUNS.
NO ERRORS.
ONE LEFT.
BOTTOM THE EIGHTH.
REDS 5, YANKEES 3.
Is this my car?
State Farm knows that for every
one of those moments...
What?
there's one of these...
Sam, I gotta go...
Is this my car?
This is ridiculous!
From car insurance...
to car loans.
State Farm is here
to help life go right.
Z2BJJZ ZVPZ
Y2BJJY YVPY
.
>> Michael: WELCOME BACK TO
GREAT AMERICAN BALLPARK.
REDS LEAD THE YANKEES 5-3 IN THE
BOTTOM OF THE EIGHTH INNING.
WE KIND OF GAVE YOU THE
BLUEPRINT.
THEY SAY GET A LEAD EARLY AND
THEN TURN IT OVER TO THE
BULLPEN.
SO FAR SO GOOD.
>> Paul: THEIR BULLPEN YOU CAN
SEE STRONG.
HIGH VELOCITY GUYS.
THE YANKEES HAD A COUPLE
OPPORTUNITIES, BUT THEY HAVE NOT
BEEN ABLE TO CASH IN.
VERY CLOSE GAME, THOUGH.
GOT THREE MORE OUTS.
>> Michael: C.C. HAD A ROUGH
SECOND INNING.
>> Paul: HE SURE DID.
HE COULD HAVE JUST BLOWN UP.
HE GOT THROUGH IT.
HE KEPT THEM IN A POINT WHERE
THEY CAN STILL GET BACK INTO
THIS GAME.
>> Michael: JACK GREEN ON FOR
THE YANKEES.
MATT HOLLIDAY TAKES OVER AT
FIRST BASE FOR CARTER.
FOULED OFF BAY PERAZA.
THESE ARE THE NUMBERS.
FIVE STARTS.
4.73.
33 STRIKEOUTS.
26 2/3 INNING.
HE WAS IN THE BATTLE AT SPRING
TRAINING FOR ONE OF THE STARTING
SPOTS THAT HAPPENED TO BE OPEN
IN THE YANKEE ROTATION.
JUST AFTER LUIS SEVERINO WHO HAS
DONE A VERY, VERY GOOD JOB.
2-2.
SWING AND A MISS.
95 MILE AN HOUR FASTBALL.
IF YOU WANT TO LOOK AHEAD TO THE
NINTH INNING TO THE YANKEES, IT
WILL BE TORREYES, HICKS, AND
BECAUSE OF A DOUBLE SWITCH,
WE'VE GOT HOLLIDAY BATTING
THIRD.
FLY BALL INTO CENTER FIELD.
EYE NICE RUNNING PLAY BY
ELLSBURY.
HE DROPPED THE BALL.
AND MESORACO WILL REACH.
ELLSBURY GOT THERE BUT DROPPED
THE BALL.
>> Paul: I THOUGHT HE MADE THE
PLAY.
JUGGLED IT COMING DOWN.
JUMP ON THE BALL.
STEPS TO THE SIDE.
DIDN'T QUITE GET DOWN DEEP
ENOUGH INTO THAT POCKET.
>> Michael: IN THE NFL THAT
WOULD HAVE COUNTED AS A FUMBLE.
AND THERE'S A STRIKE.
YOU'VE GOT HOLDER AND WARREN IN
THE YAFRPG -- YANKEE PEN.
MESORACO GETS A BASE HIT.
GREEN HAD 12 GAMES WITH THE
YANKEES.
EIGHT STARTS LAST YEAR.
PITCHED TO A 4.73 E.R.A.
HAD 52 STRIKEOUTS AND 45 2/3
INNINGS PITCHED.
RIGHT BACK TO GREEN.
HE GOES TO SECOND.
THAT'S ALL THEY'LL GET.
SCORE 1-4 AS CASTRO TOOK THE
THROW.
>> Paul: LOOKED LIKE A LITTLE
MISCOMMUNICATION TO SECOND BASE.
USUALLY YOU'RE TELLING THE
PITCHER WHO'S COVERING.
YOU'VE GOT BOTH MOVING TOWARDS
THE PLAY.
EASY PLAY FOR DIDI TO GO ACROSS
THE BAG.
NOT ABLE TO GET THE BALL OUT OF
HIS GLOVE.
>> Michael: HERE'S BILLY
HAMILTON.
RUNNER ON FIRST BASE.
TWO OUTS NOW.
FROM THE LEFT-HANDED SIDE
HAMILTON.
.361.
THE MAJOR LEAGUE AVERAGE IS 4.62
SO HE CAN FLY.
THAT'S WHY WHAT HAPPENED THE
LAST TIME UP WAS SO IMPRESSIVE.
HE GOT THROWN OUT TRYING TO
STRETCH HIS SINGLE INTO A DOUBLE
BY BRETT GARDNER.
>> Paul: EVERYBODY IN THE WORLD
KNOWS WHAT HE WANTS TO
ACCOMPLISH WHEN HE GETS ON THE
BASE IS TO STEAL BASES.
IT MAKES IT MUCH HARDER.
CATCHERS ARE CALLING FASTBALLS.
HAMILTON 19 OUT OF 21 STOLEN
BASES THIS YEAR.
>> Michael: GREEN GOT CALLED UP
AFTER THE 18-INNING MARATHON AT
WRIGLEY FIELD BECAUSE EVERYONE
BUT TOMMY WAYNE WAS USED AND
THEY WERE USED A LOT OF PITCHES
AND A LOT OF INNINGS.
SO THEY WANT TO GET GREEN UP
HERE JUST IN CASE THEY NEEDED A
LONG MAN.
JASON SHREVE GOT THE WIN IN THAT
GAME.
3-0 NOW ON HAMILTON.
AND THE PITCH.
STRIKE.
>> Paul: HIS APPROACH TO
HITTING, I MEAN, IF YOU REALLY
WATCH HIM FROM THE SIDE, IT'S SO
IMPORTANT IF YOU WATCH HIS LEFT
HAND.
YOU DON'T WANT ANY KIND OF LOOP.
WHEN YOU SEE THAT, SEE HOW HE
LOOPS AT THE BALL.
YOU WANT HIM TO STAY ON TOP OF
THE BALL WHERE HE CAN KEEP THE
BALL ON THE GROUND TO THE LEFT
SIDE OF THE INFIELD.
IT'S SOMETHING HE'S BEEN WORKING
ON.
SOMETHING THAT'S GOING TO ALLOW
HIM TO USE HIS SPEED.
ANYTIME YOU SEE THAT LEFT HAND
KIND OF LOOP UNDER THE BALL,
HE'S GOING TO HIT A FLY BALL.
THAT'S NOT WHAT BILLY HAMILTON
WANTS.
>> Michael: THE RUNNER WAS GOING
ON 3-1 BUT WAS FOUL BALL.
3-2 AND TWO OUTS.
>> Paul: YOU SHOULD BE
AGGRESSIVE ON TOP OF THE BALL
AND JUST WATCH THAT BALL.
THOSE HANDS COME UNDER THE BALL.
MAKES ALL THE DIFFERENCE IN THE
WORLD.
YOU WANT THAT IF YOU'RE AARON
JUDGE BECAUSE YOU WANT TO, YOU
KNOW, GET THAT BALL IN THE AIR.
HAMILTON, DIFFERENT TYPE OF
HITTER.
>> Michael: RUNNER GOES.
3-2.
SWING AND A MISS.
GOT HIM.
THAT WILL DO IT IN THE EIGHTH.
ONE MAN LEFT.
CAN THE YANKEES RALLY IN THE
NINTH?
THE REDS LEAD 5-3.
it.
You may never even sit
in the back seat.
Yeah, but maybe you should.
♪  ♪
(Laughter)
[ Dog whimpers ]
Man: Let's go!
Man #2: We're not coming out!
Man #1: [ Sighs ]
Flo: [ Amplified ]
I got this.
Guys, I know being
a first-time homeowner is scary,
but you don't have to do this.
Man #2: What if a tree
falls on our garage?
Woman: What if a tornado
rips off our roof?
Flo: You're covered.
And you've bundled
your home and auto insurance,
so you're saving a ton.
Come on.
You don't want to start your new
life in a dirty old truck.
Man #3: Hey.
Man #1: Whoa, whoa.
Flo: Sorry.
Woman: Oh.
Flo: You're safe.
You're safe now.
Woman:
I think I'm gonna pass out.
Can you stop using the bullhorn?
Flo:
I don't make the rules.
Can you stop using the bullhorn?
Every Team trains hard...
Every Team prepares to win...
But when U.S. Army Soldiers
take the field...
It's best if the other guys
don't bother showing up.
♪ ♪
See if you have what it takes at
goarmy.com/team
>> Michael: TAKE A LOOK AT THE
PREVAILING MOMENT OF THE GAME.
>> Paul: DRIVES IN THIS RBI.
MADE IT 4-2.
REDS NEVER LOOKED BACK.
>> Michael: PINCH-HITTING FOR
TORREYES.
THERE'S A STRIKE.
THEY'RE TRYING TO GET A TWO-OUT
SAVE OUT OF IT.
LOOK AT THREE SAVES OF MORE THAN
ONE INNING.
THAT'S TIED WITH THE DODGERS
JANSEN FOR THE MOST IN MAJOR
LEAGUE BASEBALL.
2-2.
DOES TH DOES NOT SEEM LIKE A
PLEASANT AT BAT FOR A GUY COMING
OFF THE BENCH.
>> Paul: YOU'RE LOOKING AT
96,
97.
THAT WAS 87.
NOT ENOUGH TIME COMING OFF THE
BENCH TO HAVE ANY KIND OF RHYTHM
WHATSOEVER.
>> Michael: FLY BALL, LEFT
FIELD.
DUVALL BACK AND HE'LL MAKE THE
PLAY.
ONE AWAY.
NEXT ON FS1 AFTER ALL THE ACTION
ON THE DIAMOND, GET I CAUGHT UP
ON A FULL NIGHT OF ACTION AROUND
THE BIG LEAGUES ON "MLB
WHIPAROUND."
OR WATCH IT LIVE ON FOX SPORTS
GO.
SO HEADLEY ON HIS 33rd BIRTHDAY
HITS A FLY BALL AS A
PINCH-HITTER FOR THE FIRST OUT.
HERE'S AARON HICKS.
PITCH IS LOW TO HICKS.
HICKS WANTS TO GET ON.
THAT WOULD BRING HOLLIDAY UP AS
THE TYING RUN.
1-1.
PRODUCER OF TONIGHT'S GAME BILL.
DIRECTOR IS JOHN MOORE.
BROADCAST ASSOCIATE LAUREN
WHITE.
THE TECHNICAL DIRECTOR IS BRIAN.
OUR TECH MANAGER IS TOM RICH.
BIG THANKS TO OUR STAYING
MANAGER AUDREY.
GREAT JOB BY EVERYBODY.
2-1.
2-2.
>> Paul: IGLESIAS CHANGING SPEED
MUCH MORE THIS INNING THAN HE
DID THE EIGHTH.
CHANGE-UP.
KIND OF SLINGS IT AND TURN ITS
OVER.
GOOD MOVEMENT DOWN.
>> Michael: AND A 2-2.
3-2.
HICKS PINCH-HIT IN THE SEVENTH
INNING.
GROUNDED OUT TO VOTTO.
SO HE'S 0 FOR 1.
AND HE WALKED HIM.
SO THE YANKEES HAVE THEIR SHOT.
THAT'S REALLY ALL YOU COULD ASK
FOR.
YOU WANT YOUR SHOT IN THE NINTH
INNING.
NOW HOLLIDAY COMES UP AS THE
TYING RUN.
>> Paul: THIS HAS BEEN SOME KIND
OF ROAD TRIP.
THEY'VE GOT THEIR SHOT.
THEY'RE GOT A SHOT TO SWEEP A
ROAD TRIP.
STARTING IN CHICAGO AND WINNING
THREE THERE AND THEN WINNING
HERE LAST NIGHT.
DAY OFF TOMORROW AND THEN A
TOUGH SERIES WITH HOUSTON COMING
INTO YANKEE STADIUM.
>> Michael: HERE'S HOLLIDAY, HIS
FIRST AT BAT OF THE NIGHT.
1-0.
AFTER THE FOUR GAMES IN SAN
FRANCISCO, THEN THE REDS GO TO
PLAY THE CUBS AT WRIGLEY AND
BRIAN PRICE SAID WE BELIEVE WE
COULD PLAY WITH ANYBODY IN OUR
DIVISION.
HE SAID THE CUBS CERTAINLY COULD
NOT GET ANY WORSE, BUT WE FEEL
GOOD ABOUT PLAYING THEM.
YANKEES HAVE THE FOUR GAMES AT
HOME AGAINST THE ASTROS, THEN
THEY GO ON THE ROAD AGAIN.
>> Paul: YOU START PLAYING
THROUGH THE SEASON, YOU GET OFF
TO A DECENT START, YOU REALLY
START TO FEEL YOURSELF AND WHERE
YOU ARE AS A TEAM WHEN YOU START
PLAYING THE TEAMS IN YOUR
DIVISION.
THE REDS HAD A GOOD ONE AGAINST
THE PIRATES.
THEY HAD A GOOD HOME STAND.
TO GO OUT ON THE ROAD AND PLAY
CHICAGO AND SOME OF THE TEAMS
THAT YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO
BEAT, GIVE YOU A REAL INDICATION
OF HOW THIS TEAM IS GOING TO DO.
>> Michael: 3-0 ON HOLLIDAY.
LET'S MANAGE.
DO YOU GIVE THE GREEN LIGHT OR
NOT?
>> Paul: I DON'T.
HE'S A PINCH-HITTER, BUT HE'S A
VETERAN HITTER.
YOU TELL HIM TO HIT AND HE MIGHT
TAKE ANYWAY.
I'M TRYING TO GET GARY SANCHEZ
UP THERE WHO'S BEEN IN THE GAME
RHYTHM WISE.
>> Michael: 3-0.
THERE'S A STRIKE.
3-1.
>> Paul: HE LOOKS LIKE HE WAS
TAKEN ALL THE WAY.
I NEVER UNDERSTAND WHY THE 3-0
PITCH THE STRIKE ZONE SEEMS A
LITTLE BIT BIGGER.
>> Michael: SEEM LIKE IT GOES
FROM 17 INCHES TO 19.
3-1.
HE WALKED HIM.
SO TWO STRAIGHT WALKS BY
IGLESIAS.
AND NOW THE TYING RUNS ARE ON
BASE.
AND GARY SANCHEZ COMES UP.
>> Paul: YOU CAN SEE THE
FRUSTRATION ON IGLESIAS.
HE ALL OF A SUDDEN HAS KIND OF
LOST COMMAND WITH EVERYTHING.
I TALKED EARLIER IN THE INNING
WHERE HE STARTED TO USE HIS
BREAKING BALL AND HIS CHANGE-UP
A LITTLE BIT MORE.
AND NOW HE'S GETTING BACK TO
WHERE HE NEEDS THAT GOOD
FASTBALL AND HE'S KIND OF LOST
HIS RELEASE FOR IT.
>> Michael: SO SANCHEZ IN THE
FIRST INNING CONNECTED FOR HIS
FIRST HOME RUN SINCE COMING OFF
THE DL.
JUST UNDER 450 FEET.
SO HE HAS TWO ON THE YEAR.
HE DIGS IN NOW WITH THE TYING
RUN AT FIRST BASE.
AARON HICKS IS AT SECOND.
YANKEES ARE DOWN 5-3.
TOP OF THE NINTH INNING.
AND MESORACO WANTS TO TALK ABOUT
IGLESIAS AND SUAREZ COMES IN TO
JOIN THEM.
SUAREZ DOING THE TRANSLATING.
AND FORMER RED CHAPMAN GETTING
LOOSE JUST IN CASE THERE'S A
BOTTOM OF THE NINTH INNING.
JUST OUTSIDE.
1-0.
HE'S LOST THE STRIKE ZONE.
RAISEL IGLESIAS.
TRYING FOR A TWO-INNING SAVE.
1-1.
>> Paul: ONE THOUGHT RIGHT HERE.
HE'S LOOKING INSIDE OF THE PLATE
RIGHT HERE.
BALL'S AWAY.
SEE EVERYTHING KIND OF OPENING
UP.
JUST LOOKING FOR THAT ONE PITCH
TO DRIVE.
HE COULD DO THAT EARLY IN THE
COUNT.
HE KIND OF BROADEN THINGS NOW
AND TRY TO PROTECT.
>> Michael: PITCHED SHARPLY AND
GRABBED BY SUAREZ.
THEY GO TO SECOND FOR THE
GAME-ENDING DOUBLE PLAY.
SO SANCHEZ HIT IT ON THE SCREW
BUT SUAREZ RIGHT THERE.
STARTS A 5-4 GAME-ENDING DOUBLE
PLAY.
>> Paul: BAD LUCK.
GARY SANCHEZ HITS IT HARD.
HAPPENS TO BE AT SUAREZ WHO
CATCHES IT.
EASY DOUBLE PLAY.
GAME OVER.
>> Michael: THE YANKEES HAVE
THEIR SIX-GAME WINNING STREAK
SNAPPED.
SANCHEZ HIT ABOUT AS HARD AS HE
COULD HIT IT AND IGLESIAS GIVES
THANKS TO THE GAME-ENDING DOUBLE
PLAY.
WELL, THAT DOLL WILL DO IT FROM
HERE IN CINCINNATI.
FOR PAUL O'NEAL, I'M MICHAEL
KAY.
LET'S GET IT TO MLP
"WHIPAROUND."
GOOD GAME HERE IN CINCINNATI.
BACK TO THE GUYS OUT IN
CALIFORNIA.
GUYS.
>> WHAT A FINISH.
HOTTEST TEAM IN BASEBALL.
COOLED OFF AS WE WELCOME YOU
INSIDE OUR FS1 STUDIOS.
BASEBALL FASTEST HOUR.
OVER THE NEXT HOUR AND FOR THE
NEXT 30 MINUTES COMMERCIAL FREE.
LOT OF HIGHLIGHTS.
HE'S ALREADY EXCITED.
I'M CHRIS MYERS.
THE CINCINNATI REDS, THE LATEST
THEY HAVE BEEN THREE GAMES
OVER .500 SINCE 2014.
IMPRESSIVE WIN FOR THEM F.
YOU'RE THE YANKEES, YOU HAVE
WHAT YOU WANTED AT THE END.
TWO MEN ON AND A HOME RUN
HITTER.
>> IT GOES TO SHOW YOU LEADING
THE A.L. EAST GARY SANCHEZ IS
BACK IN THE LINEUP.
TWO RUNNERS ON.
IT COULD HAVE BEEN ONE OF THOSE
MAG CAL THINGS.
TONIGHT IT WAS ONE OF THOSE
THINGS WHERE C.C. DIDN'T HAVE
HIS BEST STUFF TONIGHT.
CINCINNATI TOOK ADVANTAGE AND
GOT HITS EARLY IN THE GAME.
THE YANKEES NEVER QUIT.
THEY KEPT FIGHTING BACK.
>> FOR ME THE CINCINNATI REDS
OFFENSE WAS THE BIGGEST SURPRISE
AND ONE OF THE BIGGEST SURPRISES
IN BASEBALL.
NOBODY TALKED ABOUT THE OFFENSE
GOING INTO SPRING TRAINING BUT
KNOCKING THE COVER OFF THE BALL
RIGHT NOW AND BEING SET UP ON
THE TABLE WITH HAMILTON.
THEY'RE PLAYING WELL A LOT OF
HOUSE MONEY RIGHT NOW.
>> FOR THE REDS THERE WAS A
MOMENT THERE WITH THE CARDINALS
TRAILING THE MARLINS AND THE
CARDINALS A FOUR-GAME WINNING
STREAK WHERE THE REDS WOULD HAVE
MOVED INTO FIRST PLACE IN THAT
DIVISION.
CUBS PLAYING A DOUBLEHEADER.
WE HAVE ALL THAT COVERED FOR
YOU.
CLOSERS IN THE NEWS OUT OF THE
BULLPEN.
LET'S GET TO SOME OF THE
HEADLINES.
MATT HARVEY ADDRESSING THE
MEDIA.
SAYS HE'S EMBARRASSED BY HIS
ACTIONS.
WE'LL GET YOUR THOUGHTS.
AFTER A MUCH NEEDED RAINOUT, THE
CUBS GOT ALL THEY COULD HANDLE
IN THE DOUBLEHEADER AGAINST THE
ROCKIES WHO CONDITION TO LEAD IN
THE NATIONAL LEAGUE WEST AND
THEIR POWER ON DISPLAY.
THREE HOMERS LAST NIGHT.
ORIOLES A MUCH BIGGER CHALLENGE
IN GAME TWO OF THE BELL WAY
SERIES.
THAT'S WHERE WE START LOOKING AT
THE ACTION.
SECOND INNING.
JIMENEZ TURNS UP A HOME RUN TO
DANIEL MURPHY, THE NEWS
UNFORTUNATE, BRITTON IS GOING TO
BE OUT UNTIL MAYBE MID JULY.
THEY TALKED ABOUT THE INJURY.
THEY'RE GOING TO HAVE TO DO IT.
THAT'S GOING TO BE A PROBLEM FOR
BALTIMORE.
NOW TO THE HIGHLIGHTS.
SIXTH HOME RUN OF THE YEAR FOR
DANIEL MURPHY.
>> THAT'S A GOOD BALLPARK TO BE
HITTING IN RIGHT NOW.
TURN ON THAT THREE-RUN FASTBALL.
>> FIVE OF HIS SIX HOME RUNS
HAVE BEEN ON THE ROAD.
HIT SO FAR IN THE GAME HERE IN
THE FOURTH INNING.
LET'S TALK ABOUT THIS.
>> UNHITTABLE SLIDERS, DOWN IN
THE ZONE.
EVEN IF THE HITTERS HIT THIS
BALL, IT'S NOT GOING TO DO MUCH
DAMAGE WITH THIS CONTACT.
YOU'RE ABLE TO LIVE LOW AND LIVE
LONG AND MISS THOSE BATS.
>> EIGHT STRIKEOUTS.
NO HITS ALLOWED THROUGH FIVE
HERE IN THE SIXTH.
STILL WITHOUT A HIT.
SMITH CHANGES THAT.
HIS THIRD HOME RUN OF THE
SEASON.
>> HE HAD JUMPED IN THIS LINEUP
AND REALLY COME CLUTCH.
TALK ABOUT GUYS STEPPING UP IN
BIG SITUATIONS.
>> TOP OF THE EIGHTH.
TWO MEN ON.
ADAM LIND, SIXTH INNING.
>> AND RIGHT BEFORE THIS CHRIS
ISAAC SET UP TO GET THE BUNT
DOWN.
WAS UNABLE TO GET THE BUNT DOWN.
ADAM LIND PULLS HIM OUT.
>> ADAM JONES AND HE HIT HIS
FIFTH HOME RUN OF THE SEASON.
SOLO SHOT PUTS THE LEAD DOWN TO
TWO.
>> MACHADO, A FLY BALL IN FOUL
TERRITORY.
HUSTLING.
WITH THE HOME TEAM HELP.
EVERYBODY BACKED OFF FROM THAT.
>> YOU CAN ABSOLUTELY SPILL A
BEER.
>> YOU'VE GOT TO HELP OUT THE
HOME TEAM, BABY.